<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/collections/a-v-receivers.atom"/>
  <title>Warehouse - Metal</title>
  <updated>2019-05-28T12:36:17-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Warehouse - Metal</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916218998835</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:36:17-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:36:17-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sony-str-za810es-7-2-channel-hi-res-wi-fi-network-av-receiver"/>
    <title>Sony STR-ZA810ES 7.2-Ch Hi-Res Wi-Fi Network A/V Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sony</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13899_538__4_da9eaa7e-4699-423b-a629-573d1bdebaf9.jpg?v=1559061382"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sony<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            698.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Enjoy flexible connectivity, powerful configurability and renowned ES quality in this 7.2 channel 4K AV receiver with Dolby Atmos and DTS: x object-based surround sound. Add in full 4K HDR compatibility and easy IP integration with leading control systems and you have the total package of installation-friendly features and audio/video performance.</p>

<h6>7.2 channels for deeply immersive surround sound</h6>
<p>Lose yourself in every soundtrack thanks to 7.2 channels of room-filling surround sound, with 100 W of power per channel. You can connect up to two active subwoofers for even bass distribution around the room. So whether you’re watching movies, playing games, or listening to your favorite songs, you’ll enjoy a next-level entertainment experience.</p>

<h6>Dolby Atmos</h6>
<p>Atmos treats sounds as separate objects, releasing them from typical channels to move freely around and even above you, for deeply immersive surround sound.</p>

<h6>Seamless auto-calibration</h6>
<p>DCAC EX uses a stereo mic to measure speaker positioning down to the nearest centimeter, before automatically adjusting frequencies, phase, and delays for better sound positioning. It then tunes your speakers using a 31-band EQ, for a listening experience that's tailored to your room.</p>

<h6>DTS:X</h6>
<p>DTS:X can create an unlimited number of audio objects which adapt to your speakers in real time, to give you total immersion in every movie soundtrack.</p>

<h6>Enjoy consistent 4K content</h6>
<p>Maintain 4K quality from source to screen—the 4K pass-through feature allows data to pass through the receiver without compromising image quality, and is HDCP 2.2-compatible.</p>

<h6>See more with 4K upscale</h6>
<p>Video upscaling gives you higher quality and more visible detail, so you can see more detail in everything.</p>

<h6>6 x HDMI inputs, 2 x HDMI outputs</h6>
<p>Bring all your home theater together. With 6 HDMI inputs you can connect an Internet TV box, Blu-ray Disc™ player and games console all at once, and still have room to expand.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<p>Enjoy flexible connectivity and high-fidelity sound from this 7.2-channel 4K AV receiver with Dolby Atmos® and DTS:X object-based surround sound. eARC1314 lets you enjoy these latest audio formats with one-cable HDMI connection from your compatible TV. Add in full 4K HDR compatibility and easy IP integration with leading control systems and you have the total package of installation-friendly features and audio/video performance.</p>
<ul>
<li>High-Resolution Audio capable</li>
<li>100W per channel power output</li>
<li>4K upscaling HDMI, 6-in, 2-out</li>
<li>Dolby Atmos® and DTS:X compatible</li>
<li>4K pass-through, HDCP 2.2 compatible</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:130</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sony</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$500 to $800</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916218998835</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">698.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SON-692802-STR-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916205432883</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:52-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:52-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-vsx-lx301-7-2-channel-networked-av-receiver-with-built-in-bluetooth-and-wi-fi"/>
    <title>Pioneer VSX-LX301 7.2-Ch Networked A/V Receiver with Built-In Bluetooth and Wi-Fi</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/cf527b1ec9b2c638ad84b561b487f4be_faee3599-f41d-403d-82ba-d75090c777c5.jpg?v=1559060574"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            700.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The VSX-LX301 features Dolby Atmos and DTS:X audio formats for fully-immersive surround sound. Connect to all your favorite music sources with support for the latest Dual Band Wi-Fi network connections to stream Google Cast, TuneIn, Deezer, and Tidal. The new 384kHz/32 bit DAC provides superior playback of all music resolutions from MP3s to Hi-Res audio files. Support for multi-room audio allows sources connected to the AV receiver to be played back in different rooms.</p>

<p>Google Cast, TIDAL, and Deezer require future firmware update. Deezer currently not available in US.</p>

<h6>DTS:X Ready</h6>
<p>DTS:X leverages object-based audio to enable immersive audio experiences. It automatically adapts audio to the existing channels and speaker system, so no specific speaker layout is required. Experience a soundscape with incredibly rich and life-like audio.</p>

<h6>General Specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>170 W/ch (6 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 0.9 %, 1ch Driven FTC)</li>
<li>100 W/ch (8 ohms, 20 Hz-20 kHz, THD 0.08 %, 2ch Driven FTC)</li>
<li>Ultra HD Pass-through with HDCP 2.2</li>
<li>Built-in Wi-Fi and Bluetooth</li>
<li>MCACC Auto Room Tuning</li>
<li>Dolby Atmos</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:280</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$500 to $800</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916205432883</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">700.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SAM-864377-43--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916205334579</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:44-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:44-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-vsx-lx103-elite-7-2-channel-network-a-v-receiver"/>
    <title>Pioneer VSX-LX103 Elite 7.2-Ch Network A/V Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/81fod-rsyyl._sl1500_46c1b819-d339-4aba-9a33-eeb06728b916.jpg?v=1559060570"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            499.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Featuring 5.2.2ch surround sound with Dolby Atmos and DTS:X optimized by MCACC, and spectacular view by Ultra HD video, HDR10, HLG, and Dolby Vision, the VSX-LX103 brings the thrills of the movie theater to your home. What's more, Flare Connect offers wireless multi-room audio with easy control on the Pioneer Remote App for various sources including vinyl records. Songs from internet radio and network streaming services can also be enjoyed with Chromecast built-in and DTS Play-Fi via your smartphone.</p>

<h6>Works with Sonos</h6>
<p>The awesome home theater you’ve built around your Elite receiver can now be part of your existing Sonos Home Sound System, or the start of a new one.</p>
<p>After a simple set up, your Elite A/V receiver will seamlessly tie into Sonos, instantly waking, changing inputs and playing at the volume you command through the familiar Sonos app.</p>

<h6>Dolby Atmos/Dolby Surround Upmixing</h6>
<p>Reproduce object-oriented sound in smooth, curving movements, or the realistic three-dimensional movement overhead by the top speakers. Other audio codecs including DTS formats can be upmixed using Dolby Surround for enjoying 3D surround sound.</p>

<h6>Next Generation Video Standard Ready</h6>
<p>All HDMI terminals support 4K (60p/4:4:4/24-bit), Wide Color Gamut (BT.2020), and HDCP 2.2, so you will have no problem when upgrading to new devices.</p>

<h6>Chromecast built-in</h6>
<p>Control audio from anywhere in the house using Chromecast enabled apps running on your personal device. The VSX-LX103 also works with the Google Assistant, so you can give voice commands via Google Assistant built-in devices such as Google Home to operate the AV receiver without lifting a finger.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Direct energy amplification at 170 W/Ch (6 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 10 %, 1Ch Driven)/ 80 W/Ch (8 ohms, 20 Hz-20 kHz, THD 0.08 %, 2Ch Driven, FTC)</li>
<li>4K Ultra HD pass-through with HDCP 2.2, Dolby vision compatible with HDR10, hlg and BT.2020 support (4K/60p/4: 4: 4/24-bit) and 1080p to 4K upscaling</li>
<li>Your Pioneer receiver can now be part of your existing Sonos Home Sound System, or the start of a new one. Instantly upgrade the music streaming capability of your home theater receiver with Sonos Connect and a free firmware update.</li>
<li>Ready for surround sound tracks with Dolby Atmos, Dolby Surround Upmixer, DTS:X, DTS Neural:X Upmixer and more</li>
<li>Multi-room audio with Chromecast built-in, DTS Play-Fi and Flare Connect</li>
<li>Music, Pandora, Spotify, Tidal, and Deezer music-streaming services ready and tune in internet radio</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:192</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916205334579</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">499.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-587425-VSX-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204613683</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:27-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:27-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-slim-audio-video-component-receiver-vsx-s520"/>
    <title>Pioneer Slim Audio &amp; Video Component Receiver Black (VSX-S520)</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/12973_849__2_af411f77-6937-4c5a-a2e9-11e9dbbf4221.jpg?v=1559060553"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            399.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Bringing quality sound and the latest Features in a slim and stylish design, thanks to a highly-efficient class D amplifier. Enjoy spectacular images with Ultra HD (4K/60p/4:4:4) upscale/pass-through, play Hi-Res audio via USB/network, listen to internet radio and various streaming services, or cast music with chrome cast built-in. The slim, stylish design and efficient power makes the VSX-S520 an ideal addition to any home Cinema, It is 120v.</p>

<h6>Built-in Dual Band Wi-Fi</h6>
<p>Enjoy network features such as audio streaming via wireless LAN connection. The built-in Wi-Fi is dual band, supporting both 5 GHz and 2.4 GHz frequency channels. By using the 5 GHz band, you can enjoy steady and uninterrupted streaming of audio files.</p>

<h6>Ultra HD Upscaling/Pass-Through with HDCP 2.2</h6>
<p>The feature lets you take advantage of the highest-quality video source for viewing on a 4K TV. With support for HDCP 2.2, you can enjoy premium content such as 4K videos with digital copy protection on a compatible display.</p>

<h6>Next Generation Video Standard Ready</h6>
<p>The VSX-S520 is ready for the next generation video standard HDR (High Dynamic Range) and BT.2020, which were adopted by Ultra HD Blu-ray. HDR is a technology that drastically expands the brightness peak, providing a higher contrast between light and dark images, which creates even more life-like pictures. BT.2020 is a new color-recording technology allowing a much wider gamut than the current BT.709 standard, enabling vividly rich coloration.</p>

<h6>MCACC Auto Room Tuning</h6>
<p>Create the optimum acoustic environment with Pioneer’s MCACC (Multi-Channel Acoustic Calibration System), developed with the expertise of professional recording studios. With the custom microphone, the system automatically compensates for differences in speaker size, level and distance, and equalizes response. As an innovative solution for the phase lag between the subwoofer and the main channel speakers caused by the network filter, Phase Control compensates the delayed bass to improve sound synchronization.</p>

<h6>Multi-room Audio Offers a Variety of Ways to Enjoy Music</h6>
<p>The VSX-S520 will support FireConnect Powered by Blackfire with a future firmware update. FireConnect is a stable wireless protocol that streams audio from a compatible Pioneer AV Receiver to a compatible Pioneer wireless speaker. Enjoy Bluetooth audio, front USB audio files and internet radio from the FireConnect compatible Pioneer AV receiver to an optional FireConnect compatible Pioneer wireless speaker(s) located in another room(s).</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Slim, 2.76” low-profile design 5.1 Ch network A/V receiver featuring MCACC room calibration. Dolby Atoms: 3.1.2Ch</li>
<li>Ultra HD pass-through (4K UltraHD 60p/4: 4: 4/HDR.10/BT.2020) with HDCP 2.2 and 4K upscaling (1080p to 4K)</li>
<li>Highly-efficient class D amplifier driving 80 W/Ch (4 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 1.0 %, 1Ch Driven FTC); 50 W/Ch (4 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 1.0 %, 2Ch Driven FTC)</li>
<li>Music file playback: MP3, WMA, AAC, Apple lossless, WAV, FLAC, AIFF, DSD via USB and network (Up to 192kHz/24-bit). sound delay (Lip Sync): 500 ms at 48K/ 400 ms at 96K/ 200 ms at 192K</li>
<li>Enjoy limitless streams of your favorite online music and internet radio stations including Spotify and for the first time tune in, Tidal, and Deeper</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:245</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204613683</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">399.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-108512-SLI-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203171891</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:21:57-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:21:57-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-elite-slim-receiver-audio-video-component-receiver-sx-s30"/>
    <title>Pioneer SX-S30 Elite Slim Receiver Audio &amp; Video Component Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13120_704__1_e925be8b-8a59-4b3f-a872-ef8d8cce230d.jpg?v=1559060521"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            449.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>With the Pioneer Elite SX-S30 you can enjoy various audio entertainment including Hi-Res audio files, music streaming services, internet radio, CDs, and vinyl records. Being equipped with Bluetooth wireless technology, airplay, and built-in Wi-Fi, you can wirelessly stream songs. With the built in Class-D amplification and thin design, this network receiver can fit in small places. If you have a streaming device, you can listen to songs by plugging them to the HDMI terminal. Just connect the speaker of your choice, and play and listen the way you like.</p>

<h6>Hi-Res Audio File Playback via USB/Network</h6>
<p>You can play up to 5.6 MHz DSD (Direct Stream Digital) files, and up to 192 kHz/24-bit WAV, FLAC, AIFF, and Apple Lossless files from a USB device or via wired or wireless network.</p>

<h6>Versatile Connectivity</h6>
<p>The SX-S30 is equipped with the phono (MM) input for a vinyl record player, as well as optical and coaxial digital inputs for connecting other audio sources. The HDMI (HDCP 2.2) terminal lets you connect to your streaming devices’ and enjoy audio streaming.</p>

<h6>Connect with AirPlay and Wi-Fi</h6>
<p>After connecting your SX-S30 to your home network, you can control/access your music library with the remote control, or play music from your phone or tablet using AirPlay.</p>

<h6>Wireless Multi-room Audio</h6>
<p>The SX-S30 will support FireConnect Powered by Blackfire with a future firmware update. FireConnect is a stable wireless protocol that streams audio from a compatible Pioneer Receiver to a compatible Pioneer wireless speaker x 2. Enjoy Bluetooth audio, front USB audio files and internet radio from the FireConnect compatible Pioneer receiver to an optional FireConnect compatible Pioneer wireless speaker(s) located in another room(s).</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>5 W/Ch (4 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 1.0 %, 1Ch Driven) 2-ch network receiver with Class-D amplification</li>
<li>Built-in Bluetooth and Wi-Fi (dual band 5 GHz/2.4 GHz). Apple airplay Certified with Pandora, Spotify, Tidal, and Deezer music streaming services ready</li>
<li>HDMI 4 in/1 out (HDCP 2.2)</li>
<li>Hi-Res Audio file playback via USB/network and phono (mm) input for a vinyl record player</li>
<li>Chromecast built-in and DTS Play-Fi technology (via future firmware updates)</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__label1:New</s:tag>
    <s:tag>__stock:108</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203171891</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">449.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-450969-ELI-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201861171</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:21:13-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:21:13-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-sr8012-surround-receiver"/>
    <title>Marantz SR8012 Surround Receiver</title>
    <s:type>Home Cinema</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/81njrne9l7l._sl1500.jpg?v=1559060478"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Home Cinema<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            2999.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Experience the peak of Marantz AV expertise in the new flagship SR8012 – the first-ever 11.2-channel Marantz receiver that raises the bar for home theater. Envelop yourself in thrilling and immersive surround sound with Dolby Atmos, DTS:X and Auro 3D, the latest codecs able to drive overhead speakers for a true 3D sound experience. The receiver's 11 high-quality amplifier stages enhance audio performance via carefully selected high-grade audio components including Marantz Hyper Dynamic Amplifier Modules, or HDAMs, used in Current Feedback topology. These pass the signal to the power stages, each providing 205W of pure Marantz power and finesse to drive a full 7.1.4-channel home cinema setup without the need for additional external amplifiers.</p>

<p>And the SR8012 uses advanced Marantz sound-tuning throughout, drawing in features from the company's Reference two-channel models, including a copper chassis and an oversized, shielded toroidal transformer built to Marantz specification — plus high-current main power supply capacitors also made to the Marantz engineers' exacting standards.</p>

<p>With built-in HEOS technology, the SR8012 becomes a part of a HEOS wireless multi-room music network, enabling you to enjoy your favorite music anywhere around your home. Explore, browse, and play music from your music library, online streaming music services, or thousands of internet radio stations, using the free HEOS app.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>11.2 channel AV Receiver with 205W per channel – Enough power to fill big rooms with renowned Marantz sound</li>
<li>Latest HDMI standard for future-proof compatibility – 4K/60 Hz full-rate pass-through, 4:4:4 color resolution, HDR, BT.2020, Dolby Vision and HLG (Hybrid Log Gamma) pass-through</li>
<li>High-end build-quality for the ultimate in audio performance – Single board per channel power amplifier design; centrally mounted, oversized toroidal transformer; copper-plated chassis</li>
<li>Extended connectivity: ready to feed a TV and projector in parallel, and even a display in a second room – Eight HDMI inputs (including one front) with full HDCP 2.2 support; Three HDMI outputs (including Zone 2)</li>
<li>HD video quality from existing DVDs or analog sources – Analog to HDMI conversion and SD to HD/4K Upscaling</li>
<li>Immersive 3D sound with effects from overhead – Dolby Atmos (up to 7.1.4 or 9.1.2), DTS:X™, and Auro-3D built-in</li>
<li>Access to almost unlimited online music sources – AirPlay, Bluetooth, Internet Radio, Spotify Connect, TIDAL, Deezer and more</li>
<li>Hassle-free installation, setup and operation – Color-coded speaker terminals, Setup Assistant, Marantz 2016 AVR Remote App</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:260</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_More than $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201861171</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">2999.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-289236-SR8-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201795635</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:21:08-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:21:08-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-sr6013-9-2-channel-full-4k-ultra-hd-network-av-surround-receiver-heos"/>
    <title>Marantz SR6013 9.2-Ch Full 4K Ultra HD Network A/V Surround Receiver HEOS</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/16468_948__1_f0874d9f-741a-462e-a4f3-a1feb89021d4.jpg?v=1559060472"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            1499.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Immerse yourself in premium sound and multi-dimensional audio with the Marantz SR6013 9.2 channel AV receiver. It features Dolby Atmos, DTS:X and DTS Virtual:X decoding for immersive home theater, and proprietary HDAM circuit boards for more detailed, dynamic sound. Eight HDMI inputs are fully compatible with the latest specifications, including 4K Ultra High Definition video, 60Hz video, HDR, Dolby Vision and Hybrid Log-Gamma.</p>

<p>Listen to all your favorite music from your smart devices via Bluetooth, AirPlay or the HEOS app. Control the SR6013 with your voice and Amazon Alexa — download the HEOS Home Entertainment skill and ask Alexa to play, pause or stop music, switch inputs for your different media players, turn up the volume and more.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Now available – Apple AirPlay 2</li>
<li>9.2 channel AV Receiver with 110 W per channel (8 Ohm, 20 Hz - 20 kHz, 0.08% 2ch Drive)</li>
<li>8 HDMI inputs (incl. 1 front) with full HDCP 2.2 support; 3 HDMI outputs</li>
<li>Analog to HDMI conversion and full rate 4K Upscaling</li>
<li>4K/60 Hz full-rate pass-through, Dolby Vision compatibility, HDR, HLG and BT.2020</li>
<li>Three-dimensional audio formats Dolby Atmos, DTS:X (up to 7.1.4 with an external 2ch amplifier) and DTS Virtual:X for height virtualization effects</li>
<li>eARC (Enhanced Audio Return channel) supports the transmission of 3D audio from your TV apps with a single HDMI connection</li>
<li>Stream music from Internet Radio, Spotify Connect, Pandora, SiriusXM, Amazon Music, TIDAL, Deezer and more with Bluetooth, Airplay2 or HEOS built-in</li>
<li>Built-in Wi-Fi with 2.4GHz/5GHz dual band support</li>
<li>Enjoy multi-room whole-home audio streaming with HEOS technology</li>
<li>Amazon Alexa voice control via the HEOS Home Entertainment skill</li>
<li>Marantz 2016 AVR remote app for control over the latest generation of Marantz network AV Receivers. Available on iOS and Android.</li>
<li>High Resolution DSD (2.8/5.6MHz), FLAC, ALAC and WAV support</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:206</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$800 to $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201795635</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">1499.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-514243-SR6-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201697331</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:21:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:21:00-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-sr5013-7-2-channel-av-receiver"/>
    <title>Marantz SR5013 7.2-Ch A/V Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/16467_682__2_05639d9a-dc25-4634-b5f0-a2b07cc1fd44.jpg?v=1559060466"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            999.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Enjoy high-definition home theater and multi-dimensional surround sound with the Marantz SR5013 7.2 channel AV receiver. It features Dolby Atmos, DTS:X and DTS Virtual:X decoding for immersive home theater, and proprietary HDAM circuit boards for more detailed, dynamic sound. Eight HDMI inputs are fully compatible with the latest specifications, including 4K Ultra High Definition video, 60Hz video, HDR, Dolby Vision and Hybrid Log-Gamma (HLG; via future firmware update).</p>

<p>Listen to all your favorite music from your smart devices via Bluetooth, AirPlay or the HEOS app. Control the SR5013 with your voice and Amazon Alexa — download the HEOS Home Entertainment skill and ask Alexa to play, pause or stop music, switch inputs for your different media players, turn up the volume and more.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>7.2 channel discrete power amplifier, 100W per channel (8-ohm, 20Hz – 20kHz, 0.08% THD)</li>
<li>8 HDMI inputs — including one HDMI input on the front panel — with full HDCP 2.2 support, plus two HDMI outputs</li>
<li>4K/60 Hz full-rate pass-through, 4:4:4 color resolution, HDR and BT.2020, plus Dolby Vision compatibility and Hybrid Log-Gamma (HLG)</li>
<li>Supports object-based audio formats Dolby Atmos, DTS:X and DTS Virtual:X processing</li>
<li>Ability to decode high-resolution audio ALAC, FLAC and WAV lossless files up to 24-bit/192-kHz — plus DSD 2.8MHz and 5.6MHz tracks let you enjoy music exactly as the artist intended</li>
<li>Marantz proprietary HDAM circuit boards for more detailed, dynamic sound</li>
<li>Built-in HEOS wireless multi-room audio technology</li>
<li>Amazon Alexa voice control via the HEOS Home Entertainment skill</li>
<li>Stream the most popular music services — like Spotify, Pandora, TuneIn, Deezer and many others — via Bluetooth, AirPlay 2 or the HEOS app</li>
<li>Now available – Apple AirPlay 2</li>
<li>Integrated Phono input to connect to your turntable</li>
<li>Optimize your audio experience with Audyssey MultEQ, Dynamic Volume and Dynamic EQ for a seamless setup within your listening environment</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:108</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$800 to $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201697331</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">999.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-845669-SR5-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201304115</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:20:22-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:20:22-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-av-audio-video-component-receiver-nr1608-works-with-alexa"/>
    <title>Marantz A/V Audio &amp; Video Component Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/14098_554__2_c074a653-91a5-4a86-a26c-fffc1f11bec9.jpg?v=1559060432"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            499.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>A thrilling high-quality AV receiver occupying minimal space: that's the NR1608. High current discrete power amplifiers on all 7 channels deliver astonishing power and clarity, and it delivers immersive 3D surround sound thanks to both Dolby Atmos and DTS:X decoders, yet at just a little more than 3 inches tall it’s slim enough to slip into any TV cabinet. It’s fully compatible with the latest HDMI and HDCP 2.2 specifications on all 8 HDMI inputs, and will pass all the latest video formats – 4K 60Hz video, 4:4:4 Pure Color sub-sampling, BT.2020, HDR and Dolby Vision – from Blu-ray players, set-top boxes, games consoles and streamed/download 4K Ultra HD content to an Ultra HD TV or projector. For future HDR broadcast content, HLG (Hybrid Log Gamma) pass-through will also be supported via a firmware update.</p>

<p>Bluetooth and AirPlay can stream music directly from portable devices, while HEOS wireless multi-room music integration allows the NR1608 to become part of a complete home-wide music system. Explore and play your own music library, online streaming music services and thousands of Internet radio stations, using the free HEOS app.</p>

<p>Bluetooth and AirPlay can stream music directly from portable devices, while HEOS wireless multi-room music integration allows the NR1608 to become part of a complete home-wide music system. Explore and play your own music library, online streaming music services and thousands of Internet radio stations, using the free HEOS app.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>7-channel discrete power amplifier, 50W per channel (8 ohm, 20 Hz – 20 kHz, 0.08% THD).</li>
<li>4K/60 Hz full-rate pass-through, 4:4:4 color resolution, HDR and BT.2020, plus Dolby Vision compatibility and Hybrid Log Gamma (HLG; via future firmware update)</li>
<li>8 HDMI inputs (incl. 1 front) with full HDCP 2.2 support</li>
<li>Dolby Atmos (up to 5.1.2) and DTS:X</li>
<li>Built-in Wi-Fi with 2.4GHz/5GHz dual band support</li>
<li>HEOS wireless multiroom integration</li>
<li>AirPlay 2, Bluetooth, TuneIn Internet Radio, Pandora, Spotify, Tidal, Deezer, Amazon Prime Music, SiriusXM, Napster, iHeartRadio, Sound Cloud, Network Audio Streaming</li>
<li>Now available – Apple AirPlay 2</li>
<li>DSD (2.8/5.6MHz), FLAC, ALAC and WAV support</li>
<li>Audyssey MultEQ, Dynamic Volume and Dynamic EQ</li>
<li>Intelligent ECO mode with off/on/auto setting</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:270</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201304115</id>
      <title>Works with Alexa</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">499.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-740121-AV--WO</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201304115</id>
      <title>Classic</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">499.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-274406-AV--CL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201009203</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:20:08-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:20:08-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-av-audio-video-component-receiver-nr1508"/>
    <title>Marantz NR1508 A/V Audio &amp; Video Component Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/14097_988__1_13986810-a209-4c08-98bb-390c1343026f.jpg?v=1559060420"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            399.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>A thrilling high-quality AV receiver occupying minimal space: that's the NR1608. High current discrete power amplifiers on all 7 channels deliver astonishing power and clarity, and it delivers immersive 3D surround sound thanks to both Dolby Atmos and DTS:X decoders, yet at just a little more than 3 inches tall it’s slim enough to slip into any TV cabinet. It’s fully compatible with the latest HDMI and HDCP 2.2 specifications on all 8 HDMI inputs, and will pass all the latest video formats – 4K 60Hz video, 4:4:4 Pure Color sub-sampling, BT.2020, HDR and Dolby Vision – from Blu-ray players, set-top boxes, games consoles and streamed/download 4K Ultra HD content to an Ultra HD TV or projector. For future HDR broadcast content, HLG (Hybrid Log Gamma) pass-through will also be supported via a firmware update.</p>

<p>Bluetooth and AirPlay can stream music directly from portable devices, while HEOS wireless multi-room music integration allows the NR1608 to become part of a complete home-wide music system. Explore and play your own music library, online streaming music services and thousands of Internet radio stations, using the free HEOS app.</p>

<p>Bluetooth and AirPlay can stream music directly from portable devices, while HEOS wireless multi-room music integration allows the NR1608 to become part of a complete home-wide music system. Explore and play your own music library, online streaming music services and thousands of Internet radio stations, using the free HEOS app.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>7-channel discrete power amplifier, 50W per channel (8 ohm, 20 Hz – 20 kHz, 0.08% THD).</li>
<li>4K/60 Hz full-rate pass-through, 4:4:4 color resolution, HDR and BT.2020, plus Dolby Vision compatibility and Hybrid Log Gamma (HLG; via future firmware update)</li>
<li>8 HDMI inputs (incl. 1 front) with full HDCP 2.2 support</li>
<li>Dolby Atmos (up to 5.1.2) and DTS:X</li>
<li>Built-in Wi-Fi with 2.4GHz/5GHz dual band support</li>
<li>HEOS wireless multiroom integration</li>
<li>AirPlay 2, Bluetooth, TuneIn Internet Radio, Pandora, Spotify, Tidal, Deezer, Amazon Prime Music, SiriusXM, Napster, iHeartRadio, Sound Cloud, Network Audio Streaming</li>
<li>Now available – Apple AirPlay 2</li>
<li>DSD (2.8/5.6MHz), FLAC, ALAC and WAV support</li>
<li>Audyssey MultEQ, Dynamic Volume and Dynamic EQ</li>
<li>Intelligent ECO mode with off/on/auto setting</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:42</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201009203</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">399.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-388788-AV--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916200845363</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:20:01-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:20:01-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-audio-video-receiver-audio-video-component-receiver-sr7012-works-with-alexa"/>
    <title>Marantz SR7012 A/V Receiver Audio &amp; Video Component Receiver, Works with Alexa</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/14645_926__3_09586a4d-b72b-4297-9a6f-6fee95e14156.jpg?v=1559060407"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            999.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Marantz has long set the standard for AV receivers combining home theatre prowess with superb music ability, and the SR7012 takes that capability to unprecedented levels, combining the very latest technology for an immersive movie experience, including full 4K compatibility and unparalleled 3D surround sound decoding, with precision audio engineering and tuning.</p>

<p>Marantz doesn’t believe that home cinema performance should come at the expense of music playback, and the SR7012 is designed to sit at the heart of a complete high-end home entertainment system, with nine powerful amp channels built-in. It has a wide range of facilities to enable your favourite music to be shared and enjoyed, including network streaming, compatibility with ultra-high-resolution music formats, Bluetooth and Airplay for playback from portable devices, and the HEOS wireless multiroom system.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>9.2 channel AV Receiver with 200 W per channel</li>
<li>4K/60 Hz full-rate pass-through, 4:4:4 color resolution, HDR, BT.2020 , Dolby Vision and HLG (Hybrid Log Gamma) pass-through</li>
<li>8 HDMI inputs (incl. 1 front) with full HDCP 2.2 support; 3 HDMI outputs (incl. Zone 2)</li>
<li>Analogue to HDMI conversion and SD to HD/4K Upscaling</li>
<li>Dolby Atmos (up to 7.1.4 with an external 2ch amplifier), DTS:X™, and Auro-3D built-in</li>
<li>Built-in Wi-Fi with 2.4GHz/5GHz dual band support</li>
<li>Built-in HEOS Wireless Multi-Room Audio Technology</li>
<li>AirPlay 2, Bluetooth, Internet Radio, Spotify Connect, TIDAL, Deezer and more</li>
<li>Now available – Apple AirPlay 2</li>
<li>DSD (2.8/5.6MHz), FLAC, ALAC and WAV support</li>
<li>Audyssey MultEQ XT32, LFC, Sub EQ HT, Dynamic Volume and Dynamic EQ</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__label1:New</s:tag>
    <s:tag>__stock:108</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$800 to $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916200845363</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">999.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-639142-AUD-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916164833331</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T11:53:07-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T11:53:07-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/denon-avrx2400h-7-2-channel-av-receiver-with-built-in-heos-wireless-technology-works-with-alexa"/>
    <title>Denon AVR-X2400H 7.2-Ch A/V Receiver with Built-In HEOS Wireless Technology, Works with Alexa</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Denon</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/71ppksx-cfl._sl1500.jpg?v=1559058792"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Denon<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            399.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The AVR-X2400H 7.2 channel AV Surround Receiver delivers incredibly immersive surround sound, plenty of amplifier power and unparalleled music playback options, thanks to our built-in HEOS technology, Apple AirPlay 2, and Amazon Alexa voice compatibility for seamless control.</p>

<em>Now available – voice control with Amazon Alexa, Siri via Apple AirPlay 2, and Google Assistant</em>

<h6>Amazing 3D Sound</h6>
<p>Enjoy a superb surround sound experience with the latest audio formats including Dolby Atmos and DTS:X. The AVR-X2400H’s 7 amplifier design means, you can run two dedicated overhead speakers in a 5.1.2 configuration. Exclusive DTS Virtual:X™ adds the complete immersive experience regardless the number of speakers installed.</p>

<h6>Ready for the future of Home Cinema</h6>
<p>The AVR-X2400H’s advanced video section is fully compatible with the latest HDMI and HDCP 2.2 specifications and prepared for any 4K Ultra HD source. High Dynamic Range (HDR), Dolby Vision compatibility and Hybrid Log Gamma (HLG, via firmware update) are also available.</p>

<h6>Powerlful 7.2 Channel AMP with Eco Mode</h6>
<p>Featuring high current discrete power output devices on all channels, the AVR-X2400H delivers high power and is rated at a maximum of 150 watts per channel. There’s also an Auto Eco mode that adjusts the maximum power available according to the volume level as well as an on-screen Eco metre that lets you see the power consumption reduction in real time.</p>

<h6>The Heart of your Wireless Network</h6>
<p>Every sound, all your music, controlled effortlessly. Full wireless connectivity is provided via both Wi-Fi and Bluetooth and Apple Airplay 2 is supported. The built-in HEOS technology allows the AVR-X1400H to become the app-controlled heart of a whole-house wireless multi-room sound network.</p>

<h6>Perfect setup from the start</h6>
<p>The AVR-X2400H easily guides you through the set-up process to ensure the most accurate configuration. Optimise all settings for the best possible sound and video quality with your system from the get-go.</p>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:241</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Denon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916164833331</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">399.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>DEN-605340-AVR-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916164702259</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T11:53:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T11:53:00-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/denon-avrs930h-7-2-channel-av-receiver-with-built-in-heos-wireless-technology-works-with-alexa"/>
    <title>Denon AVR-S930H 7.2-Ch A/V Receiver with Built-In HEOS Wireless Technology, Works with Alexa</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Denon</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13510_713__1_9e5569c0-65ee-46be-95e8-87718b2f8b7c.jpg?v=1559058786"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Denon<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            299.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The AVR-S930H is the most advanced Denon S Series home entertainment solution with a complete set of next-generation audio and video features. Thanks to the built-in HEOS wireless technology, you can stream and control all your local or online music effortlessly from anywhere in your home with the comfortable HEOS App. Create a stunning home theater experience with the Dolby Atmos and DTS:X 3D surround sound decoders, and all the latest video technologies including Dolby Vision, HDR (High Dynamic Range) and 4K Scaling. With the second HDMI output, you can even enjoy AV sources in a another room.</p>

<h6>Powerful 7 channel Discrete Amplifier with Eco Mode</h6>
<p>Featuring high current discrete power output devices on all channels, the AVR-S930H delivers high power and is rated at a maximum of 185 watts per channel. There's also an Auto Eco mode that adjusts the maximum power available according to the volume level as well as an on-screen Eco meter that lets you see the power consumption reduction in real time. For compatibility with the widest range of loudspeakers the AVR-S930H is equipped with low impedance drive capability that provides operational stability with 4 ohm speakers.</p>

<h6>Dolby Atmos</h6>
<p>Feel every dimension in Dolby Atmos. Dolby Atmos transports you into the story with moving audio that flows all around you with breathtaking realism. Enjoy a 5.1 surround sound speaker system and 2 additional overhead speakers or 2 Dolby Atmos elevation speakers for the ultimate home theater experience - including Dolby Surround upmixer for legacy content.</p>

<h6>DTS:X</h6>
<p>DTS:X™ immersive audio places sound where it would occur naturally in space, creating a lifelike, multi-dimensional audio experience in the home. The improved immersion and heightened realism draw you into the world of your favorite movies. The included spatial remapping engine, DTS Neural:X™, gives your movie, game and music collections a new lease on life! DTS:X brings the theater home.</p>

<h6>HEOS Wireless Multi-Room Music Streaming</h6>
<p>Our HEOS technology enables the AVR-S930H to become part of the HEOS wireless multi-room system, allowing you to enjoy your favorite music anywhere – and everywhere – around your home. Share music stored on your home network, Internet radio or streaming services with HEOS wireless speakers, or even other HEOS-capable receivers, throughout the house. And it's all controlled by the free HEOS app, installed on as many smartphones and tablets as you like! The app gives you instant multi-room audio control, meaning you can command music in every room from any device: play different music from different sources in every room, group several rooms together and play the same song, perfectly synchronized, in party mode!</p>

<h6>High Resolution Audio / Front USB Port</h6>
<p>Enjoy superb audio fidelity with your favorite high resolution audio tracks. The AVR-S930H features high resolution audio decoding with multiple lossless file types including ALAC, FLAC and WAV at up to 24-bit/196-kHz along with compatibility for 2.8/5.6-MHz DSD files (DSD is the audio coding format of SACD). Play them from memory devices via the front panel USB, or from network sources – the AVR-S930H will also play lossy file types such as MP3 and WMA.</p>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:193</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Denon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916164702259</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">299.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>DEN-241191-AVR-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916164669491</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T11:52:54-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T11:52:54-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/denon-avr-x8500h-13-2-channel-av-receiver"/>
    <title>Denon AVR-X8500H 13.2-Ch A/V Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Denon</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/991bd65d343914dd46d33e070da6748c_78eee7d7-c109-4bc3-825c-2324705ea10c.jpg?v=1559058777"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Denon<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            3999.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The Denon Flagship AVR-X8500H powers the next generation of home theater with the world’s first 13.2 channel receiver that supports the latest immersive audio formats, including IMAX Enhanced, Dolby Atmos, DTS:X and unparalleled music playback options, thanks to our built-in HEOS technology, Apple AirPlay 2, and Amazon Alexa voice compatibility for seamless control.</p>

<h6>Powerful 13.2 channel Home Theater Experience</h6>
<p>The AVR-X8500H ushers in a leading-edge home theater experience with 13.2 channels that support the latest surround sound formats and 4K Ultra HD picture.</p>

<h6>Supports the latest surround audio formats</h6>
<p>Immerse yourself in multi-dimensional sound — the Denon AVR-X8500H powers IMAX Enhanced, Dolby Atmos, DTS:X. Auro-3D will be enabled via future firmware update at no additional charge.</p>

<h6>Ready for the future of Home Theater</h6>
<p>The AVR-X8500H’s advanced video section is fully compatible with the latest HDMI and HDCP 2.2 specifications and prepared for any 4K Ultra HD source. High Dynamic Range (HDR), Dolby Vision compatibility, Hybrid Log Gamma (HLG) and eARC (enhanced Audio Return Channel) are supported as well. You can also enjoy ultra-high-definition pictures from legacy analog and digital sources.</p>

<h6>The Heart of your Wireless Network</h6>
<p>Every sound, all your music, controlled effortlessly. Full wireless connectivity is provided via Bluetooth and Wi-Fi. The AVR-X8500H works with Apple Airplay and Amazon Alexa, bringing cutting-edge voice control and incredible sound to all your home entertainment. The built-in HEOS technology allows the AVR-X8500H to become the app-controlled heart of a whole-house wireless sound network.</p>

<h6>Perfect setup from the start</h6>
<p>The AVR-X8500H easily guides you through the set-up process to ensure the most accurate configuration and lets you optimize all settings for the best possible sound and video quality. The most advanced Audyssey MultEQ XT32 room measurement system guarantees the best sound in every room.</p>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:95</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Denon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Silver</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_More than $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916164669491</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">3999.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>DEN-895212-AVR-BL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916164669491</id>
      <title>Silver</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">3999.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>DEN-254165-AVR-SI</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916164603955</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T11:52:48-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T11:52:48-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/denon-avr-x4500h-9-2-ch-high-power-4k-av-receiver-with-amazon-alexa-voice-control"/>
    <title>Denon AVR-X4500H 9.2 Ch High Power 4K A/V Receiver with Amazon Alexa Voice Control</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Denon</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/8b4d3ee815ae775a5785334d42f8e310_5439764f-2494-4b4b-96ec-025e0ec4283e.jpg?v=1559058773"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Denon<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            1599.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The 9.2 channel AVR-X4500H 4K AV receiver supports IMAX Enhanced, Dolby Atmos, DTS:X and Auro-3D for an immersive home theater experience. The advanced HDMI section of the AVR-X4500H (8 in, 3 out) features the latest video technologies, including Dolby Vison, HDR10, HLG, 4K video upscaling and HDCP 2.2 processing on all ports. Stream music from Spotify®, Pandora®, Tidal and more with AirPlay2 and HEOS built-in; control your home theater and music services with your voice through Amazon Alexa. Ideal for custom integrations, the AVR-X4500H features “ihiji Invision” and “Domotz Pro” remote system monitoring and management technology, plus an award-winning Setup Assistant for a seamless out-of-box experience.</p>

<h6>Powerful 9-channel Amplifier</h6>
<p>Featuring discrete high-current amplifiers on all channels, the AVR-X4500 delivers high-power performance at 125 watts per channel (8 ohms, THD 0.05%, 20Hz~20kHz). Low impedance drivers provide operational stability for a wide range of speakers and create a balanced, tonal sound. The AVR-X4500H features three-dimensional sound formats Dolby Atmos, DTS:X, DTS Virtual:X and Auro-3D, plus an HDMI section with HDCP 2.2 support and advanced video processing with 4K scaling for HDMI sources and two 12V trigger outputs to connect external devices.</p>

<h6>Supports the latest surround audio formats</h6>
<p>Immerse yourself in multi-dimensional sound — the Denon AVR-X4500H powers IMAX Enhanced, Dolby Atmos, DTS:X, and Auro-3D.</p>

<h6>Ready for the future of Home Theater</h6>
<p>All eight HDMI inputs — and three HDMI outputs — feature HDCP 2.2 support that lets you enjoy copy-protected content uninhibited. Watch movies and shows with 4K Ultra HD 60Hz video, 4:4:4 Pure Color sub sampling, Dolby Vision, High Dynamic Range (HDR10), Hybrid Log-Gamma (HLG), eARC (enabled via firmware update) 21:9 video, 3D and BT.2020 passthrough support for exceptional color, clarity and contrast.</p>

<h6>The Heart of your Wireless Network</h6>
<p>Every sound, all your music, controlled effortlessly. Full wireless connectivity is provided via Bluetooth and Wi-Fi. The AVR-X4500H works with AirPlay2 and Amazon Alexa, bringing cutting-edge voice control and incredible sound to all your home entertainment. The built-in HEOS technology allows the AVR-X4500H to become the app-controlled heart of a whole-house wireless sound network.</p>

<h6>Perfect setup from the start</h6>
<p>The AVR-X4500H easily guides you through the setup process to ensure the most accurate configuration. Optimize all settings for the best possible sound and video quality with your system from the get-go. The most advanced Audyssey MultEQ XT32 room measurement system provides the best sound in every room and with the Audyssey MultEQ Editor app, go under the hood and set the AVR to your exact specifications.</p>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:284</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Denon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_More than $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916164603955</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">1599.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>DEN-174796-AVR-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916164538419</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T11:52:42-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T11:52:42-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/denon-avr-s920w-7-2-channel-full-4k-ultra-hd-av-receiver-with-bluetooth-wi-fi"/>
    <title>Denon AVR-S920W 7.2-Ch Full 4K Ultra HD A/V Receiver with Bluetooth &amp; Wi-Fi</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Denon</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/11810_788__1_8fd14199-6419-4228-9164-cf6c78ab6acc.jpg?v=1559058766"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Denon<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            299.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Immerse yourself in incredible surround sound with the AVR-S920W 7.2 channel AV receiver which features Dolby Atmos surround sound decoding, delivering breathtaking surround sound with today's advanced movie soundtracks. With Dolby Atmos you'll experience the same revolutionary 3D surround sound found in premium movie theaters with the ability to create an overhead surround soundfield that dramatically expands the sonic space. Via a future firmware update the AVR-S920W will also able to decode DTS:X soundtracks that deliver an immersive 3-dimensional soundspace.</p>

<p>Prepared for the future, the AVR-S920W features an advanced video processing and signal handling system including the latest HDMI 2.0a specification that's compatible with 4K Ultra HD BT.2020 full rate 60 Hz content, HDR (High Dynamic Range), 4:4:4 Pure Color sub-sampling and 21:9 aspect ratio pass-through. It's also HDCP 2.2 compliant, which is a requirement for 4K Ultra HD copy-protected content.</p>

<p>Full wireless connectivity is provided by both Bluetooth and dual band Wi-Fi with dual diversity antennas that ensure robust signal transmission and reception. Stream your favorite audio tracks wirelessly to the AVR-S920W and easily control it with the Denon 2016 AVR remote available for iOS, Android and Kindle Fire smart devices.</p>

<p>You can also enjoy the latest uncompressed high resolution audio tracks as the AVR-S920W decodes AIFF, ALAC, FLAC and WAV files at up to 24-bit/192-kHz resolution, along with 2.8/5.6-MHz DSD high resolution tracks.</p>


<h6>Dolby Atmos</h6>
<p>Dolby's revolutionary Atmos surround sound technology dispenses with channel-based coding in favor of more advanced object-based coding, giving the soundtrack designer the ability to precisely place sounds anywhere in the 3-dimensional space. Now you can enjoy this same award-winning technology at home with the AVR-S920W that lets you to connect a 5.1 surround sound speaker system and 2 additional overhead speakers or 2 Dolby Atmos elevation speakers for the ultimate home theater experience. Along with Dolby Atmos decoding the AVR-S920W also features Dolby TrueHD lossless decoding and other Dolby Digital technologies.</p>

<h6>DTS:X</h6>
<p>The latest immersive surround sound system, DTS:X features object-based audio coding that lets the soundtrack designer place sonic elements anywhere in the 3D acoustic soundspace, and provides for overhead speakers to deliver a stunning surround sound experience. Along with DTS:X decoding, the AVR-S920W features DTS-HD Master Audio decoding and other DTS audio technologies. DTS:X decoding will be available via a future firmware update.</p>

<h6>Latest HDMI 2.0a Connectivity; HDCP 2.2 Compatible; 4K Ultra HD BT.2020</h6>
<p>Featuring 8 HDMI inputs, including 1 conveniently located on the front panel along with dual HDMI outputs, the AVR-S920W incorporates an advanced video section that features the latest HDMI 2.0a specification including support for 4K Ultra HD BT.2020 60 Hz full rate video, High Dynamic Range (HDR), Wide Color Gamut, 4:4:4 Pure Color sub-sampling and 21:9 video pass-through along with support for 3D content. The AVR-S920W also features HDCP 2.2 compatibility, a requirement for 4K Ultra HD copy-protected content.</p>

<h6>Smart TV Connectivity</h6>
<p>When you connect the AVR-S920W to your Smart TV you have the option of controlling the AVR-S920W via the HDTV's remote control which lets you select an input, adjust the volume and choose the surround sound mode.</p>

<h6>Multi-Room Listening</h6>
<p>You can configure the AVR-S920W for a 7 channel home theater surround system or you can choose to have a 5 channel surround system in the main room with 2 of the amplifier channels dedicated to drive separate stereo speakers in another room. Enjoy a surround sound movie in the home theater room while others can enjoy stereo sound from a different source in a second room at the same time.</p>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:153</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Denon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916164538419</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">299.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>DEN-841038-AVR-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916164472883</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T11:52:36-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T11:52:36-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/denon-avr-s730h-7-2-channel-full-4k-ultra-hd-av-receiver"/>
    <title>Denon AVR-S730H 7.2-Ch Full 4K Ultra HD A/V Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Denon</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13509_829__1.jpg?v=1559058761"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Denon<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            479.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The AVR-S730H represents the most affordable seven channel 3D Audio AV Receiver with renowned original Denon sound. With HEOS wireless technology built-in, you can stream and control all your local or online music effortlessly from anywhere in your home with the comfortable HEOS App. Create a stunning home theater experience with the built-in Dolby Atmos and DTS:X 3D surround sound decoders, and all the latest video technologies including Dolby Vision, HDR (High Dynamic Range) and HDCP 2.2. The ultimate in future-proofness.</p>

<h6>Powerful 7 channel Discrete Amplifier with Eco Mode</h6>
<p>Featuring high current discrete power output devices on all channels, the AVR-S730H delivers high power and is rated at a maximum of 165 watts per channel. There's also an Auto Eco mode that adjusts the maximum power available according to the volume level as well as an on-screen Eco meter that lets you see the power consumption reduction in real time. For compatibility with the widest range of loudspeakers the AVR-S730H is equipped with low impedance drive capability that provides operational stability with 4 ohm speakers.</p>

<h6>Dolby Atmos</h6>
<p>Feel every dimension in Dolby Atmos. Dolby Atmos transports you into the story with moving audio that flows all around you with breathtaking realism. Enjoy a 5.1 surround sound speaker system and 2 additional overhead speakers or 2 Dolby Atmos elevation speakers for the ultimate home theater experience - including Dolby Surround up-mixer for legacy content.</p>

<h6>DTS:X</h6>
<p>DTS:X™ immersive audio places sound where it would occur naturally in space, creating a lifelike, multi-dimensional audio experience in the home. The improved immersion and heightened realism draw you into the world of your favorite movies. The included spatial remapping engine, DTS Neural:X™, gives your movie, game and music collections a new lease on life! DTS:X brings the theater home.</p>

<h6>HEOS Wireless Multi-Room Music Streaming, Controlled by Free HEOS App</h6>
<p>Our HEOS technology enables the AVR-S730H to become part of the HEOS wireless multi-room system, allowing you to enjoy your favorite music anywhere – and everywhere – around your home. Share music stored on your home network, Internet radio or streaming services with HEOS wireless speakers, or even other HEOS-capable receivers, throughout the house. And it's all controlled by the free HEOS app, installed on as many smartphones and tablets as you like! The app gives you instant multi-room audio control, meaning you can command music in every room from any device: play different music from different sources in every room, group several rooms together and play the same song, perfectly synchronized, in party mode!</p>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:151</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Denon</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916164472883</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">479.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>DEN-364406-AVR-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
