<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/collections/headphones.atom"/>
  <title>Warehouse - Metal</title>
  <updated>2019-05-28T12:37:59-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Warehouse - Metal</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916220735539</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:37:59-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:37:59-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sony-xb950-extra-bass-wireless-headphones-with-app-control"/>
    <title>Sony XB-950B1 Extra Bass Wireless Headphones with App Control</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sony</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13261_147__1_2e3211f9-de49-4919-9e67-006800a5c5a0.jpg?v=1559727794"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sony<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            128.00 - 178.00
            <a href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sony-xb950-extra-bass-wireless-headphones-with-app-control">(3 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Feel the freedom and love the bass with these Bluetooth headphones with EXTRA BASS that deliver powerful, clear sound and up to 18 hours of battery life. Find the perfect sound for each song with the Sony Headphones Connect app, while you enjoy broad frequency response for the ultimate listening experience. Even take hands-free calls with the built-in mic. Freedom has never sounded better.</p>
<h6>Bass that moves you</h6>
<p>Feel more than just the beat. EXTRA BASS™ enhances all your low-end frequencies for deep power on every track. Just touch the Bass Effect button to get started.</p>
<h6>Long-lasting wireless freedom</h6>
<p>Listen wirelessly over Bluetooth® technology with NFC™ one-touch pairing for up to 18 hours, even with EXTRA BASS™ turned on.</p>
<h6>Fine-tuned by you</h6>
<p>Set the perfect sound for every song. Sony | Headphones Connect app lets you adjust your bass levels and gives you presets for outdoor stage, club, hall, or arena-style sound.</p>
<h6>Specifications and features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Explore your favorite tracks in new depth with EXTRA BASS™ and listen wirelessly over Bluetooth® wireless technology for up to 18 hours</li>
<li>EXTRA BASS™ for deep, punchy sound</li>
<li>High-quality audio with Bluetooth® wireless technology</li>
<li>Optimize your sound settings with Sony | Headphones Connect app</li>
<li>18 hours of battery life</li>
<li>USB rechargeable, cable included</li>
<li>Driver Unit: 1.57", Dome</li>
<li>
</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:237</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sony</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Blue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Red</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916220735539</id>
      <title>Blue</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">128.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SON-544136-XB950-BL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916220735539</id>
      <title>Red</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">178.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SON-791030-XB950-RE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916220735539</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">178.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SON-781000-XB950-BL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916220637235</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:37:49-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:37:49-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sony-wh1000xm3-wireless-industry-leading-noise-canceling-over-ear-headphones"/>
    <title>Sony WH1000XM3 Wireless Industry Leading Noise Canceling Over-Ear Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sony</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/16850_260__2_333029c0-868f-451c-9a9a-290b2e4dcd76.jpg?v=1559727709"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sony<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            348.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Sony industry-leading noise cancellation evolves to further immerse you in your music. The addition of Sony proprietary HD noise canceling processor Qn1 masterfully eliminates the noise around you. Listen all day with up to 30 hours of battery life. Quick charging gives five hours of playback with just a 10-minute charge.</p>

<p>WH-1000XM3 headphones take you even deeper into silence with further improvements to our industry-leading noise cancellation, and smart listening that adjusts to your situation.</p>

<h6>Experience the next level of silence</h6>
<p>See what happens when it's just you and your music, with noise canceling that cuts more outside sound than ever before. And experience how smart headphones can be with advanced noise-canceling technology such as Adaptive Sound Control, and the convenience of smart features including Quick Attention, Voice Assistant compatibility and touch control.</p>

<h6>More power = even less noise</h6>
<p>With our new HD Noise-Canceling Processor QN1, noise-canceling power is greatly enhanced. Having a dedicated NC processor also ensures the reproduction of your music is never compromised due to processor performance.</p>

<h6>Smart listening by SENSE ENGINE – automatically adjusts to your situation</h6>
<p>See how Adaptive Sound Control automatically detects your activity such as traveling, walking, and waiting, then adjusts ambient sound settings to you. And with Quick Attention, you can communicate without removing your headphones — simply place your hand over the housing to turn the volume down for instant conversation.</p>

<h6>Automatically adjusts to whatever you do</h6>
<ul>
<li>Traveling: take trips without interruption and lose yourself in music with no background noise</li>
<li>Walking: be aware of everything around you, from street to office, while still enjoying music</li>
<li>Waiting: hear important announcements while you wait with reduced background noise</li>
</ul>

<h6>Wear all day in total comfort</h6>
<p>Super soft, pressure-relieving earpads in foamed urethane evenly distribute pressure and increase ear pad contact for a stable fit. Comfort is further enhanced by a larger and deeper ergonomic ear space structure. And with a lighter weight design, your music is the only thing you’ll notice all day.</p>

<h6>Smarter than your average headphones</h6>
<p>Everything is at your fingertips. Answer hands-free phone calls with a double tap - or change tracks, adjust the volume and make calls by touching or swiping the panel. And help from your phone’s voice assistant is just one long press away.</p>

<h6>All day power and quick charging</h6>
<p>With a huge 30 hours of battery life, you'll have enough power even for long trips away. And if you need to charge in a hurry, you can get five hours' worth of charge after just ten minutes with the optional AC adapter.</p>

<h6>Specifications and features:</h6>
<p>WH-1000XM3 headphones take you even deeper into silence with further improvements to our industry-leading noise cancellation1, and smart listening that adjusts to your situation.</p>
<ul>
<li>HD Noise-Canceling Processor QN1 lets you listen without distractions</li>
<li>Unique automatic personal NC, and Atmospheric Pressure optimization</li>
<li>Wireless freedom with Bluetooth® technology and NFC</li>
<li>Smart Listening by Adaptive Sound Control automatically adjusts ambient sound to your activity</li>
<li>High-quality audio with DSEE HX™ and LDAC</li>
<li>Driver Unit: 1.57 ", dome type (CCAW Voice coil)</li>
<li>DSEE HX: Yes</li>
<li>Input(s): Stereo Mini Jack</li>
<li>Frequency Response: 4 Hz-40,000 Hz</li>
<li>Passive Operation: Yes</li>
<li>NFC: Yes</li>
<li>Cord Lenght: headphone cable (approx. 3.94 ft, OFC strands, gold-plated stereo mini plug)</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:209</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sony</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Champagne</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Silver</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916220637235</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">348.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SON-886186-WH1-BL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916220637235</id>
      <title>Silver</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">348.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SON-959960-WH1-SI</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916218605619</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:35:46-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:35:46-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sony-rf995rk-wireless-rf-headphones"/>
    <title>Sony RF995RK Wireless RF Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sony</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/14882_007__1_0bb8bd50-6357-4f63-95db-e8c835aad522.jpg?v=1559061356"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sony<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            118.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Zone out and tune in with these wireless, Noise-Reducing home headphones that deliver high quality, detailed sound and a range of up to 150 feet. Watch privately and without distraction, while voice control lets you focus on every word of your favorite movies and shows. Listen longer with up to 20 hours of battery life and enjoy a design that's built for comfort. Let the binge watching begin.</p>

<h6>Zone out and tune in to uncompromised sound</h6>
<p>Lose yourself in a world of quality sound with these home theater wireless headphones. Noise-reducing technology keeps the wireless signal free of interference from other electronic devices, so you can enjoy your favorite film, soundtrack, or game with crystal-clear sound.</p>

<ul>
<li>Wireless range: 150ft. The enhanced range from the transmitter dock lets you move from room to room without losing an audio connection.</li>
<li>Enjoy your favorite shows, music, and films without having to charge for up to 20 hours.</li>
<li>Whatever you’re watching, hear every detail in crystal clarity with dynamic 1.57" drivers.</li>
</ul>

<h6>Freedom to roam, throughout your home.</h6>
<p>With a long battery life and wide reception range, you can take your favorite films and shows with you as you wander around your home—so you'll never miss out on the action again.</p>

<h6>Surround yourself with high-quality sound</h6>
<p>With a closed cap design, dynamic drivers, and Voice Mode button, sound quality is increased while noise and distractions from the outside world are reduced—leaving you to enjoy your entertainment in peace.</p>

<h6>Relax and get comfortable</h6>
<p>Whether it's a box-set binge or a movie marathon, these soft and secure headphones are optimized for comfortable, long listening—so any family member can sit in total comfort for hours.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<p>Lose yourself in a world of uncompromising sound with these home wireless headphones. Noise-reducing technology puts you in the center of your favorite film, series, or game with minimal distractions.</p>
<ul>
<li>Wireless closed-type headphones with a range of up to 150 ft</li>
<li>Noise reduction system reproduces a clearer sound</li>
<li>1.57" driver unit delivers a wide frequency range</li>
<li>Built-in automatic tuning for high quality transmission</li>
<li>Listen for longer with up to 20 hours of battery life</li>
<li>Driver Unit: 1.57 in</li>
<li>Frequency Response: 10 Hz-22,000 Hz</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:136</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sony</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916218605619</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">118.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SON-890031-RF9-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916217884723</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:34:49-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:34:49-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sony-mdrxb650bt-b-extra-bass-bluetooth-headphones"/>
    <title>Sony MDRXB650BT Extra Bass Bluetooth Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sony</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/12585_998__1_b566f0db-0ebd-4187-9af3-2564a8aa69aa.jpg?v=1559728017"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sony<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            128.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Let your music loose with the powerful, clear sound of EXTRA BASS and freedom of Bluetooth connectivity that lets you cut the cord, while pumping it up in style. Never miss a beat with 30mm drivers engineered for today's bass-heavy tracks and up to 30 hours of battery life. Even take hands-free calls. They're ready to hit the streets with bass that hits.</p>

<ul>
<li>Connect and stream music easily with Bluetooth and NFC</li>
<li>Connectivity Technology: Wireless</li>
<li>Feel the powerful, clear sound of Extra Bass</li>
<li>Keep the music pumping with up to 30 hours of battery life</li>
<li>Listen in comfort and style with cushioned ear pads</li>
<li>Enjoy hands-free calls with a built-in mic</li>
</ul>

<h6>Connect and stream music easily with Bluetooth and NFC</h6>
<p>Enjoy easy, one-touch connectivity and music streaming with NFC. No NFC? No problem. Connect via Bluetooth and you’re ready to go.</p>

<h6>Feel the power of Extra Bass</h6>
<p>Made for today’s heavy-hitting bass lines and dropping beats, Extra Bass technology delivers powerful, clear bass sound where it’s hardest to find—in portable speakers and headphones. The result is a full, deep, resonating sound that’s perfect for EDM, Hip-Hop and other music. So push the button, crank it up and let the bass drop.</p>

<h6>Keep the music pumping with long battery life</h6>
<p>A four-hour charge gives you up to 30 hours of continuous playback—so you can keep on listening, track after track, mix after mix.</p>

<h6>Listen in comfort and style</h6>
<p>The self-adjusting headband and soft, cushioned ear cups offer the long-lasting comfort you need for listening to your favorite albums back-to-back. And they look good doing it, too.</p>

<h6>Enjoy hands-free calls</h6>
<p>A built-in button and mic on the headband enables you to take hands-free calls from selected smartphones while listening to music. Switch easily between songs and calls with no need to remove your headphones.</p>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:167</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sony</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Blue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916217884723</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">128.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SON-119184-MDR-BL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916217884723</id>
      <title>Blue</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">128.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SON-232650-MDR-BL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916217786419</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:34:44-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:34:44-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sony-mdr100abn-b-headphones"/>
    <title>Sony MDR-100ABN/B H.ear Wireless Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sony</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/12268_696__1_2df6cef7-01da-4753-97f5-4636f9f95c94.jpg?v=1559061288"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sony<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            348.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>No distracting background noise. No annoying cables. Just pure, authentic sound. Get ready to lose yourself in the music. The h.ear range combines High-Resolution Audio capability with bold, distinctive design. Vibrant sound has never looked so good.</p>

<h6>Choose your Color</h6>
<p>The h.ear on Wireless NC headphones come in a range of distinctive colors. Which one will you go for?</p>
<ul>
<li>Lime Yellow</li>
<li>Viridian Blue</li>
<li>Charcoal Black</li>
<li>Bordeaux Pink</li>
<li>Cinnabar Red</li>
</ul>

<h6>Fits your Style</h6>
<p>The single-color, single-shape design blends signature style with form-fitting comfort. So you and your headphones are always in tune.</p>

<h6>Look and listen</h6>
<p>Premium sound, tactile materials and finishes, meticulous attention to detail. Discover h.ear on Wireless NC.</p>

<h6>Yes to freedom</h6>
<p>Bluetooth® and One-touch NFC let you listen to music wirelessly, free from the restraints of a headphone cable. And LDAC transmits approximately three times more data (at the maximum transfer rate: 990 kbps) than conventional Bluetooth® Audio, which allows you to enjoy High-Resolution Audio content in exceptional sound quality near to High-Resolution Audio.</p>

<h6>No to noise</h6>
<p>Whatever’s going on around you, Digital Noise Cancellation blocks out background noise so you can focus fully on the music.</p>

<h6>Detailed, dynamic sound</h6>
<p>Designed to support High-Resolution Audio, the headphones' 1.58 in driver units feature titanium-coated diaphragm domes for precise sound across the entire frequency range.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>High-Resolution Audio compatible</li>
<li>Easy Bluetooth® connectivity with One-touch NFC</li>
<li>Digital Noise Canceling technology</li>
<li>1.57" HD driver unit for dynamic range</li>
<li>Titanium-coated diaphragm domes minimize distortion</li>
<li>Driver Unit: 1.57 in (Dome Type)</li>
<li>Frequency Response: 5-40,000 Hz (Power On) (Wired)</li>
<li>Cord Lenght: 3.94 ft</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:271</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sony</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916217786419</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">348.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SON-668925-MDR-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916217622579</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:34:39-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:34:39-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sony-mdr-rf912rk-wireless-rf-headphones"/>
    <title>Sony MDR-RF912RK Wireless RF Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sony</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/81NFOrKFF2L._SL1500.jpg?v=1559061283"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sony<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            88.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Zone out and tune in with these wireless, noise-reducing home headphones that deliver high quality, detailed sound with a range of up to 150 feet. Watch privately and without distraction while voice mode lets you focus on every word of your favorite movies and shows. Listen longer with up to 13 hours of battery life and enjoy a design that’s built for comfort. Let the binge watching begin.</p>

<ul>
<li>Noise reduction system produces a clearer sound</li>
<li>Move freely from room to room with long wireless range</li>
<li>Listen Longer with up to 13 hours of battery life</li>
<li>Experience dynamic, detailed sound with 40mm drivers</li>
<li>Self-adjusting headband for listening comfort</li>
</ul>

<h6>Zone out and tune in</h6>
<p>Noise-reducing technology keeps the wireless signal free of interference from other electronic devices, so you can enjoy your favorite film, soundtrack or game with crystal clear sound.</p>

<h6>Wireless range</h6>
<p>The enhanced range from the transmitter dock (up to 150 feet) lets you to move from room to room without losing an audio connection.</p>

<h6>Up to 13 hours of battery life</h6>
<p>Enjoy your favorite shows, music and films without having to charge for up to 13 hours.</p>

<h6>Dynamic detail with 40mm drivers</h6>
<p>From thunderous booms to soft whispers, the large 40mm drivers will make sure that you experience every detail in clear and precise sound quality.</p>

<h6>Self-adjusting headband for listening comfort</h6>
<p>Designed for long-term wear, the cushioned and comfortable ear pads are perfect for evenings spent relaxing on the sofa.</p>

<h6>Set up, sit back</h6>
<p>Once these headphones are out of the box, simply connect the transmitter dock to your TV with the supplied cable, and sit back as the headphones sync to the dock.</p>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:149</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sony</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$0 to $100</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916217622579</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">88.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SON-874422-MDR-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916216541235</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:33:58-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:33:58-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/shure-srh840-professional-monitoring-headphones"/>
    <title>Shure SRH840 Professional Monitoring Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Shure</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/12846_547__1_0a3b4889-c4ec-44d9-b171-0cd78cb65b83.jpg?v=1559061250"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Shure<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            199.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>SRH840 Professional Monitoring Headphones feature a precisely tailored frequency response that delivers rich bass, clear mid-range and extended highs.</p>

<p>Designed for professional audio engineers and musicians, the SRH840 Professional Monitoring Headphones from Shure are optimized for studio recording and critical listening.</p>

<p>A precisely tailored frequency response and 40mm neodymium dynamic drivers combine with total comfort and durability to provide the ultimate listening experience. The replaceable cable and included set of replacement ear pads ensure a long product life. Also includes threaded 1/4" (6.3mm) gold-plated adapter.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Precisely tailored frequency response delivers rich bass, clear mid-range and extended highs</li>
<li>Wide, padded headband provides ergonomic fit for superior comfort over extended periods</li>
<li>Closed-back, circumaural design rests comfortably over the ears and reduces background noise</li>
<li>Collapsible design for easy storage and portability</li>
<li>Legendary Shure quality to withstand the rigors of everyday use</li>
<li>Bayonet Clip securely locks cable into ear cup</li>
<li>Replaceable ear cup pads included to ensure long product life</li>
<li>3m (10ft) coiled detachable cable provides plenty of length and easy storage and replacement</li>
<li>Carrying bag protects headphones when on the go or not in use</li>
</ul>

<h6>Package contains:</h6>
<ul>
<li>HPAQA1 6,3 mm Thread Adapter, Gold-plated</li>
<li>HPACA1 Detachable coiled cable</li>
<li>HPACP1 Carrying Bag</li>
<li>HPAEC840 Replacement Earpads</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:128</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Shure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916216541235</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">199.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SHU-355405-SRH-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916216377395</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:33:47-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:33:47-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/shure-srh440-professional-studio-headphones"/>
    <title>Shure SRH440 Professional Studio Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Shure</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/12405_976__2_2139873a-527f-4c6c-9e7c-be6aa0eacbe4.jpg?v=1559126290"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Shure<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            99.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>SRH440 Professional Studio Headphones reproduce accurate audio across an extended range. The SRH440 Professional Studio Headphones from Shure provide exceptional sound reproduction and comfort.</p>

<em>Optimized for home and studio recording, SRH440 headphones reproduce accurate audio across an extended range.</em>

<p>Impedance, power handling and sensitivity are all calibrated for professional audio devices such as DJ mixers, mixing consoles, and headphone amplifier. Includes carrying bag and threaded 1/4" (6.3mm) gold plated adapter.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Enhanced frequency response delivers accurate audio across an extended range</li>
<li>Impedance and power handling optimized for perfomance with professional audio devices</li>
<li>Adjustable headband and collapsible construction provide comfort and portability</li>
<li>Bayonet clip securely locks detachable cable into ear cup</li>
</ul>

<h6>Package contains:</h6>
<ul>
<li>HPAQA1 Threaded ¼” gold plated adapter</li>
<li>HPACA1 Detachable coiled cable</li>
<li>HPACP1 Carrying pouch</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:270</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Shure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$0 to $100</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916216377395</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">99.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SHU-704007-SRH-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916216213555</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:33:33-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:33:33-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/shure-srh1840-professional-open-back-headphones"/>
    <title>Shure SRH1840 Professional Open Back Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Shure</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/5199_355__2_d5334ec2-0192-4a06-aa13-02070697690f.jpg?v=1559061225"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Shure<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            499.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>SRH1840 Professional Open Back Headphones feature individually matched drivers for unparalleled acoustic performance, including smooth, extended highs and accurate bass.</p>

<h6>Product Details</h6>
<p>The SRH1840 Professional Open Back Headphones feature individually matched drivers for unparalleled acoustic performance, including smooth, extended highs and accurate bass. Developed with premium materials and precision engineering, the custom-crafted design is extremely lightweight and durable. Ideal for mastering or critical listening applications.</p>
<p>The included storage case, replacement set of velour ear pads, replacement cable, and threaded adapter ensure years of uninterrupted listening enjoyment.</p>
<ul>
<li>Individually matched 40 mm neodymium drivers for unparalleled acoustic performance with smooth, extended highs and accurate bass</li>
<li>Open-back, circumaural design for exceptionally natural sound, wide stereo image, and increased depth of field</li>
<li>Lightweight construction featuring aircraft-grade aluminum alloy yoke and stainless steel grilles for enhanced durability</li>
<li>Steel driver frame with vented center pole piece improves linearity and eliminates internal resonance for consistent performance at all listening levels</li>
<li>Ergonomic dual-frame, padded headband is lightweight and fully adjustable for hours of listening comfort</li>
<li>Optimized for connection to external headphone amplification systems</li>
<li>Oxygen-free copper cable with Kevlar™ reinforced jacket for superior performance and durability</li>
<li>Dual-exit cables with gold-plated MMCX connectors provide secure connection and detachability for easy storage or replacement</li>
<li>Replaceable velour ear pads with high-density, slow-recovery foam for exceptional comfort</li>
<li>Legendary Shure durability to withstand the rigors of everyday use</li>
</ul>

<h6>Package contains:</h6>
<ul>
<li>HPAEC1840 Additional Pair of Velour Ear Pads</li>
<li>2 x HPASCA2 Detachable Cables</li>
<li>HPAQA1 Threaded ¼” Gold-Plated Adapter</li>
<li>HPACC2 Zippered Hard Storage Case</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:141</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Shure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916216213555</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">499.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SHU-788218-SRH-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214968371</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:32:23-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:32:23-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sennheiser-urbanite-on-ear-headphones"/>
    <title>Sennheiser Urbanite On-Ear Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sennheiser</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/71JHrYcD4UL._SL1440_4ffc62c6-7bd1-4b92-b8cd-975972eec97e.jpg?v=1559061147"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sennheiser<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            199.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The Sennheiser URBANITE loves your ears. This headphone delivers the goods, an intense, uncompromising performance, reflecting Sennheiser’s pursuit of perfect sound. URBANITE serves up serious club sound with massive bass and excellent clarity through the entire frequency range. Your ears are transported to centerstage with URBANITE.</p>

<p>Sennheiser URBANITE is for uncompromising ears; those that won’t settle for weak audio quality, lousy fit and lame styling. Experience the beat all over again, with bass that never sounded that good! They’re built tough with stainless steel hinges and aluminium ear cup sliders. URBANITE is made to go, just fold’em up and take them everywhere. The integrated in-line remote control and microphone let’s you take calls and control your music on smartphones and tablets, these phones keep you connected. Two versions are available, one for Apple iOS and one for Samsung Galaxy devices. Sennheiser URBANITE is the sound your ears have been waiting for.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Take the club with you - Legendary Sennheiser sound featuring massive bass, smooth midrange and extended treble</li>
<li>Tough companion - Constructed using premium extra rugged parts like stainless steel hinges and aluminum sliders for reliability and durability</li>
<li>Stay connected - control your music and calls (includes detachable cable with 3-button remote control and integrated microphone for Apple iOS devices</li>
<li>Easy to store and bring along - compact foldable design makes them easy to collapse and store in the supplied soft pouch</li>
<li>Peace of mind - 2-years international warranty when purchased from an Authorized Sennheiser dealer</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:55</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sennheiser</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214968371</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">199.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-883240-URB-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214575155</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:32:11-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:32:11-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sennheiser-pxc-480-active-noise-canceling-headphones"/>
    <title>Sennheiser PXC 480 Active Noise-Canceling Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sennheiser</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13159_569__3_efddc25a-ecac-46df-90de-36d6f4dcb957.jpg?v=1559061136"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sennheiser<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            299.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Introducing the Sennheiser PXC 480 – a premium headset for the discerning business traveller. This stylish, compact and foldable headset delivers exceptional sound quality anywhere you go. It features Sennheiser NoiseGard active noise cancellation virtually eliminating unwanted ambient sound. Ergonomically engineered for superior wearing comfort, this headset lets you escape the stresses of travel and upgrades your 'on-the-go' audio experience to first class.</p>

<h6>NoiseGard Active Noise Cancellation</h6>
<p>NoiseGard actively cancels out ambient sound creating a quieter environment to ensure uninterrupted listening. Whether on a plane, train or noisy street NoiseGard delivers effective noise suppression allowing you to relax and focus on work or entertainment in total comfort.</p>

<h6>Exceptional Battery Performance</h6>
<p>The PXC 480 delivers up to 50-hours of battery life on a single charge. This means you can travel worldwide in the comfort and tranquility ensured by active noise cancellation on a single charge. If you forget to charge the battery, the headset works passively with the remote cable both as headphone and headset.</p>

<h6>Superior Sound Quality</h6>
<p>The PXC 480 delivers Sennheiser signature sound quality. Music and movies are presented with exceptional clarity, balance and dynamics providing an immersive audio experience. When not listening to music, NoiseGard can also be used in passive mode, by simply detaching the cable to create an oasis of calm whenever needed. There’s also a 'Talk Through' feature making it easy to hear and talk to cabin crew without removing the headphone.</p>

<h6>Lightweight, Comfortable Design</h6>
<p>The PXC 480’s ergonomically engineered padded headband and memory foam cushioned ear cups provide exceptional wearing comfort for long listening sessions. The fold-flat collapsible frame enables the PXC 480 to discreetly fold away into its stylish compact travel case.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>NoiseGard active noise cancellation for suppression of plane and train noises</li>
<li>Supplied connecting cable features an in-line microphone and remote for call control</li>
<li>Compact, collapsible design makes it easy to pack for "on the go' use</li>
<li>Impedance: Active 150 Ω / Passive 45 Ω</li>
<li>Frequency response:17 - 23000 Hz</li>
<li>Sound pressure level (SPL):109 dB (1kHz/1Vrms)</li>
<li>Up to 50 hour battery life providing long listening sessions using active noise cancellation</li>
<li>Connectivity Technology: Wired</li>
<li>2 year warranty when purchased from an authorized Sennheiser dealer</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:184</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sennheiser</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Grey</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214575155</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">299.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-256434-PXC-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214411315</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:31:57-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:31:57-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sennheiser-hd-599-open-back-headphones"/>
    <title>Sennheiser HD 599 Open Back Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sennheiser</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13164_870__2_f78f20a5-174d-47ac-a181-76c4e434717f.jpg?v=1559061124"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sennheiser<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            199.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The best in class, remastered. The new HD 500 Series pushes performance to the next level. Topping the product line is the HD 599, a premium headphone for those seeking sophisticated sound, design and build quality. Powered by Sennheiser proprietary transducer technology and featuring the 'Ergonomic Acoustic Refinement' (E.A.R) design, the HD 599 represents a step into the world of audiophile sound reproduction.</p>

<p>This open back, around ear headphone delivers an impressively natural tonal balance with outstanding spatial performance. Exceptional wearing comfort is provided by large ear cups fitted with plush velour ear cushions. Premium design cues; timeless ivory color scheme, brown headband stitching and matte metallic detail, communicate quality at first glance. Crafted to impress, the HD 599 is a solid choice for music listeners with sense of discovery!</p>

<h6>Premium Components</h6>
<p>Sennheiser engineered transducers use aluminum voice coils delivering high efficiency, excellent dynamics and extremely low distortion.</p>

<h6>Open Acoustic Design</h6>
<p>Around-ear, open-back design delivers an impressively 'open' spatial presentation to improve the listening experience.</p>

<h6>Versatile Connectivity</h6>
<p>The HD 599 comes with two detachable cables: a 3m cable with a 6.3-mm jack for a home entertainment system and a shorted 1.2m cable with a 3.5mm jack perfect for use with phones, tables, and laptops.</p>

<h6>Extreme Comfort</h6>
<p>Lightweight yet robust design with luxurious velour covered ear cushions and padded headband deliver exceptional wearing comfort for long listening sessions.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Open back, around ear design</li>
<li>Connectivity Technology: Wired</li>
<li>Powered by proprietary Sennheiser 38mm, 50-ohm transducers</li>
<li>Soft, replaceable ear pads for enhanced comfort</li>
<li>Two cables included - 3m detachable cable with 6.3mm jack and 1.2m detachable cable with 3.5mm jack</li>
<li>Two year warranty when purchased from an authorized Sennheiser deale</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:242</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sennheiser</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Brown</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Champagne</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214411315</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">199.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-814658-HD--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214345779</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:31:50-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:31:50-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sennheiser-hd-579-open-back-headphones"/>
    <title>Sennheiser HD 579 Open Back Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sennheiser</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13163_128__2_dc875df2-b621-4190-9d74-cc2a8450a5af.jpg?v=1559061116"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sennheiser<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            199.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The best in class, remastered. The new HD 500 Series pushes performance to the next level. New to the product line is the HD 579, a headphone for those seeking premium performance and value. Powered by Sennheiser proprietary transducer technology and featuring the “Ergonomic Acoustic Refinement” (E.A.R) design, the HD 579 approaches the world of audiophile sound reproduction. This open back, around ear headphone delivers a natural tonal balance with outstanding spatial performance. Exceptional wearing comfort is provided by large ear cups fitted with plush velour ear cushions. The unique cool gray color scheme compliment styling that communicates quality at first glance. Crafted to impress, the HD 579 delivers performance beyond its price.</p>

<h6>Premium Components</h6>
<p>Sennheiser engineered transducers use aluminum voice coils delivering high efficiency, excellent dynamics and extremely low distortion.</p>

<h6>Open Acoustic Design</h6>
<p>Around-ear, open-back design delivers an impressively 'open' spatial presentation to improve the listening experience.</p>

<h6>E.A.R Technology</h6>
<p>'Ergonomic Acoustic Refinement' design channels audio directly into your ears producing a more 'in room' like listening experience.</p>

<h6>Extreme Comfort</h6>
<p>Lightweight yet robust design with luxurious velour covered ear cushions and padded headband deliver exceptional wearing comfort for long listening sessions.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Open back, around ear design</li>
<li>Connectivity Technology: Wired</li>
<li>Powered by proprietary Sennheiser 38mm, 50-ohm transducers</li>
<li>Soft, replaceable ear pads for enhanced comfort</li>
<li>Robust 3m detachable cable with 6.3mm jack and 3.5mm jack adaptor included</li>
<li>Frequency Response - 15- 28,000 Hz , Impedance - 50 ohm</li>
<li>Two year warranty when purchased from an authorized Sennheiser dealer</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:197</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sennheiser</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Grey</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214345779</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">199.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-320963-HD--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214247475</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:31:42-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:31:42-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sennheiser-hd-569-closed-back-headphones"/>
    <title>Sennheiser HD 569 Closed Back Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sennheiser</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13162_051__1_c5b0227b-2ac0-4bf8-bcee-e363366ee183.jpg?v=1559061109"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sennheiser<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            149.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The best in class, remastered. The new HD 500 Series pushes performance to the next level. New to the HD 500 Series product line is the HD 569, a closed-back for those needing noise isolation with outstanding sound quality. Powered by Sennheiser proprietary transducer technology and featuring the 'Ergonomic Acoustic Refinement' (E.A.R) design, the HD 569 drives toward audiophile reproduction. Being closed-back, this around ear delivers noise isolation along with a natural tonal balance. Exceptional wearing comfort is provided by large ear cups fitted with plush velour ear cushions. The stealth black color compliments classic styling quality at first glance. Shipped with two cable options, one including an in-line one-button remote with microphone, the HD 569 provides phone call control!</p>

<h6>Premium Components</h6>
<p>Sennheiser engineered transducers use aluminum voice coils delivering high efficiency, excellent dynamics and extremely low distortion.</p>

<h6>Noise Isolating</h6>
<p>Around-ear, closed-back design effectively reduces ambient noise improving the listening experience.</p>

<h6>E.A.R Technology</h6>
<p>'Ergonomic Acoustic Refinement' design channels audio directly into your ears producing a more 'in room' like listening experience.</p>

<h6>Extreme Comfort</h6>
<p>Lightweight yet robust design with luxurious velour covered ear cushions and padded headband deliver exceptional wearing comfort for long listening sessions.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Closed back, around ear design</li>
<li>Connectivity Technology: Wired</li>
<li>Powered by proprietary Sennheiser 38mm, 23-ohm transducers</li>
<li>Soft, replaceable ear pads for enhanced comfort</li>
<li>Two cables included - 3m detachable cable with 6.3mm jack and 1.2m detachable cable with 3.5mm jack with in line microphone and remote for call &amp; music control</li>
<li>Two year warranty when purchased from an authorized Sennheiser dealer</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:104</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sennheiser</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214247475</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">149.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-442980-HD--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214181939</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:31:35-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:31:35-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sennheiser-hd-559-open-back-headphones"/>
    <title>Sennheiser HD 559 Open Back Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sennheiser</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13161_370__2_abaca465-7ca7-414c-98f0-9130a16073e1.jpg?v=1559061100"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sennheiser<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            99.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>New to the HD 500 series product line is the HD 559, a headphone for those seeking exceptional value. Powered by Sennheiser proprietary transducer technology and featuring the “Ergonomic Acoustic Refinement” (E.A.R) design, the HD 559 provides the first step into the world of audiophile sound reproduction. This open back, around ear headphone delivers a natural tonal balance with outstanding spatial performance. Exceptional wearing comfort is provided by large ear cups fitted with plush velour ear cushions. The HD 559 is the ideal choice for listeners wanting performance beyond price.</p>

<h6>Premium Components</h6>
<p>Sennheiser engineered transducers use aluminum voice coils delivering high efficiency, excellent dynamics and extremely low distortion.</p>

<h6>Open Acoustic Design</h6>
<p>Around-ear, open-back design delivers an impressively 'open' spatial presentation to improve the listening experience.</p>

<h6>E.A.R Technology</h6>
<p>'Ergonomic Acoustic Refinement' design channels audio directly into your ears producing a more 'in room' like listening experience.</p>

<h6>Extreme Comfort</h6>
<p>Lightweight yet robust design with luxurious velour covered ear cushions and padded headband deliver exceptional wearing comfort for long listening sessions.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Open back, around ear design</li>
<li>Connectivity Technology: Wired</li>
<li>Powered by proprietary Sennheiser 38mm, 50-ohm transducers</li>
<li>Soft, replaceable ear pads for enhanced comfort</li>
<li>Robust 3m detachable cable and 6.3mm jack</li>
<li>Two year warranty when purchased from an authorized Sennheiser dealer</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:194</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sennheiser</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Grey</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$0 to $100</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214181939</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">99.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-197489-HD--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214083635</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:31:24-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:31:24-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sennheiser-hd-4-30g-around-ear-headphones"/>
    <title>Sennheiser HD 4.30G Around Ear Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sennheiser</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13165_832__1_5795db12-2646-4003-a489-27d81dc04d00.jpg?v=1559061091"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sennheiser<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            99.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The Sennheiser HD 4.30G is a closed back, around ear headset optimized for use with Android devices. Delivering exceptional performance and value, it combines signature Sennheiser sound with a 3-button button remote and mic located on the cable allowing music and call control. A lightweight yet durable design featuring comfortable padded ear pads and a folding headband for easy storage when not being used. The HD 4.30G is perfect for listening to music and taking calls on the go!</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Ultra lightweight on ear design ensures exceptional wearing comfort</li>
<li>Connectivity Technology: Wired</li>
<li>Detachable cable has an inline 3-button remote control and microphone allowing call and music control for Android devices</li>
<li>32mm, 18-ohm proprietary Sennheiser transducer delivers exceptional performance when used with portable audio devices, tablets and mobile phones</li>
<li>Folding headband allows the headphone to be collapsed for storage when not being used</li>
<li>2 year warranty when purchased from an authorized Sennheiser dealer</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:162</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sennheiser</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Gold</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Grey</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_White</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$0 to $100</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214083635</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">99.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-688812-HD--BL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214083635</id>
      <title>White</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">99.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-599618-HD--WH</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214018099</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:31:18-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:31:18-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sennheiser-hd-4-20s-around-ear-headphones"/>
    <title>Sennheiser HD 4.20S Around Ear Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sennheiser</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13169_897__2_a47252d4-12f5-4ef9-9c7a-12be00315ff4.jpg?v=1559061083"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sennheiser<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            79.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The Sennheiser HD 4.20s is a closed back, around ear headset delivering exceptional performance and value. It combines signature Sennheiser sound with a convenient one button remote with microphone on the cable allowing calls to be answered. A lightweight yet durable design featuring comfortable padded ear pads and a folding headband for easy storage when not being used. The HD 4.20s is perfect for listening to music and taking calls on the go!</p>

<h6>Closed Back Design</h6>
<p>Closed back, around-ear design with ergonomically designed ear pads reduces ambient noise to improve the listening experience.</p>

<h6>Single-Button Remote</h6>
<p>Cable features a single-button remote with in-line microphone for push to talk functionality and music playback.</p>

<h6>Folding Headband</h6>
<p>Folding headband allows the headphone to be collapsed for portability when on the go.</p>

<h6>Proprietary Transducers</h6>
<p>Sennheiser proprietary 32mm, 18 Ohm transducers deliver exceptional performance and compatibility with smart phones, tablets and computers.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Ultra lightweight on ear design ensures exceptional wearing comfort</li>
<li>Connectivity Technology: Wired</li>
<li>The single-button remote and microphone on the cable make it easy to take calls with your smartphone</li>
<li>32mm, 18-ohm proprietary Sennheiser transducer is ideal for use with portable audio devices, tablets and mobile phones</li>
<li>Folding headband allows the headphone to be collapsed for storage when not being used</li>
<li>2 year warranty when purchased from an authorized Sennheiser dealer</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:248</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sennheiser</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Grey</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$0 to $100</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916214018099</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">79.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-801359-HD--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916213952563</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:31:11-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:31:11-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sennheiser-gsp-500-open-acoustic-gaming-headset"/>
    <title>Sennheiser GSP 500 Open Acoustic Gaming Headset</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sennheiser</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/product_detail_x2_desktop_GSP500_01_1312x1312_28879fb1-4c1c-4e95-9e08-a62f6a7dc430.jpg?v=1559124382"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sennheiser<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            229.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The GSP 500 provides superior wearing comfort and extreme audio fidelity allowing pro’s to be immersed in their game. An open back system using Sennheiser engineered and manufactured transducers, it provides a smooth, balanced frequency response with superb detail, dynamics and extended bass response adding impact to gaming audio. Optimum transducer positioning inside the ear cups channel sound directly into your ears delivering exceptional spatial representation of the gaming environment. An advanced broadcast quality noise-cancelling microphone provides crystal clear in-game chat. A volume control is conveniently located on the earcup for intuitive use.</p>

<p> The GSP 500’s open-back, ventilated ear cup features ergonomically designed ear pads covered with soft, breathable fabric to keep ears comfortable and cool during long gaming sessions. A new ear cup hinge system is combined with an innovative adjustable headband allowing variable clamping pressure. These features establish a new benchmark in customized fit and wearing comfort. Take your game to the next level with the GSP 500!</p>

<h6>Unrivaled Audio Quality</h6>
<p>The open-back acoustic design with optimum transducer positioning inside the ear cups channel sound directly into your ears, delivering incredibly natural sound quality with an exceptional spatial presentation.</p>

<h6>Crystal-clear Communication</h6>
<p>The GSP 500’s pro-level microphone features Sennheiser's latest noise cancellation technology for crystal clear in game chat. Lifting the mic boom arm conveniently mutes the mic.</p>

<h6>Ergonomic, Breathable Ear Cups</h6>
<p>The open-back, ventilated ear cups are fitted with ergonomically shaped ear pads covered in a soft, breathable fabric. This provides superior wearing comfort and keep your ears cool.</p>

<h6>Customized Fit</h6>
<p>A new, innovative headband design features adjustable contact pressure allowing the GSP 500 to provide a customized fit for different sized heads.</p>

<h6>Outstanding Durability</h6>
<p>A robust design crafted using premium materials, including a unique metal hinge, insures impeccable long-term usability.</p>

<h6>Multi-Platform</h6>
<p>The GSP 500 is a multi-platform gaming headset compatible with PC, Mac, PS4, Xbox One, and other consoles using a 3.5 mm jack input.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>German-engineered Sennheiser transducers ensure exceptional sound quality to deliver an immersive audio experience</li>
<li>Open acoustic design, ergonomic ear pads covered in breathable fabric and advanced hinge system create a superb fit ideal for long gaming sessions in superior comfort</li>
<li>A unique headband featuring adjustable contact pressure provides a customized fit on different head sizes provides exceptional wearing comfort</li>
<li>Broadcast quality microphone with advanced noise-cancelling provides crystal-clear in-game communication. The microphone easily mutes by raising the boom arm</li>
<li>A volume control located on the right ear cup provides intuitive on-the-fly audio adjustment at your fingertips</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:198</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sennheiser</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Red</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916213952563</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">229.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-879582-GSP-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916213887027</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:31:05-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:31:05-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sennheiser-gsp-350-pc-gaming-headset-with-dolby-7-1-surround-sound"/>
    <title>Sennheiser GSP 350 PC Gaming Headset with Dolby 7.1 Surround Sound</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sennheiser</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/product_detail_x2_desktop_GSP350_1312x1312_01.jpg?v=1559124429"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sennheiser<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            139.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The Sennheiser GSP 350 gaming headset brings an incredible level of realism to PC gaming thanks to its customizable sound options including downloadable 7.1 Dolby Surround technology. Form-fitting memory foam ear pads ensure exceptional comfort and best-in-class isolation from outside distractions allowing for total focus while you play. Also on board is Sennheiser’s infamous broadcast quality, noise-cancelling microphone that minimizes background noises for crystal-clear in-game chat.</p>

<h6>7.1 Dolby Surround Sound</h6>
<p>A USB Surround Dongle provides Dolby 7.1 Surround Sound processing delivering spatial realism to enhance your game.</p>

<h6>Noise-Cancelling Microphone</h6>
<p>Experience crystal-clear game chat and convenient muting by simply lifting the microphone boom arm.</p>

<h6>XL Ear Cups</h6>
<p>Memory foam and leatherette ear pads for the best-in-class acoustic seal and comfort.</p>

<h6>Closed Back Design</h6>
<p>Prevents sound from escaping and keeps you undisturbed while playing.</p>

<h6>Tough Built</h6>
<p>Durability and reliability are ensured by the use of high-quality materials and extensive product testing.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Dolby 7.1 Surround Sound to immerse yourself in the game</li>
<li>Professional noise-cancelling microphone provides crystal clear clarity for in game chat</li>
<li>Customizable surround software let you shape the sound</li>
<li>Lift to mute microphone feature shuts off in game communication</li>
<li>Volume control on right ear cup provides “on-the-fly” level adjustment</li>
<li>Memory foam ear pads delivers best-in-class acoustic seal and comfort</li>
<li>Designed for PC gaming</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:179</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sennheiser</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Red</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916213887027</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">139.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-605913-GSP-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916213821491</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:30:58-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:30:58-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sennheiser-gsp-300-closed-back-gaming-headset"/>
    <title>Sennheiser GSP 300 Closed Back Gaming Headset</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sennheiser</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/61U_2BW3vgTWL._SL1000_65d163d3-6ebe-47bf-9bd1-200bd777bb20.jpg?v=1559124319"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sennheiser<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            99.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>For those that take their fun seriously, Sennheiser has created the GSP 300, a closed acoustic headset in a new fresh design for gamers ready to level up. Fitted with luxurious XL memory foam ear pads, the GSP 300 delivers best-in-class comfort and improved ambient noise isolation, leaving you undisturbed and focused during your gaming sessions.</p>

<h6>Perfectly Adjusted</h6>
<p>The GSP 300 is equipped with an aviation-inspired split headband which reduces pressure for the best comfort and fit even during long gaming sessions. The superior fit is further assured by a clever ball-joint hinge that makes it easy to perfectly angle the speakers to suit your face shape.</p>

<h6>Crystal-Clear Communication</h6>
<p>For the ultimate team performance, the GSP 300 is equipped with a broadcast quality noise-cancelling microphone that minimizes background noise, and a short boom arm that cuts out breathing sound for clearer in-game communication. To mute, simply lift the boom arm and you're off the air!</p>

<h6>Tough Built</h6>
<p>Durability and reliability are secured by the use of high-quality materials.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Closed back headset with memory foam ear pads providing best-in-class noise isolation and comfort</li>
<li>Sennheiser sound quality with exceptional bass performance and acoustic clarity</li>
<li>Split headband delivers superior comfort and fit. Frequency response (Headphones): 15 - 26,000 Hz</li>
<li>Broadcast quality noise-cancelling microphone can be muted by raising the boom arm</li>
<li>Intuitive volume control on right ear cup for on-the-fly adjustments</li>
<li>Closed acoustic gaming headset for PC, Mac, PS4 and Xbox One</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:264</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sennheiser</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Blue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$0 to $100</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916213821491</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">99.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-775848-GSP-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916213723187</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:30:52-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:30:52-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sennheiser-cx-sport-bluetooth-sport-in-ear-headphones"/>
    <title>Sennheiser CX Sport Bluetooth Sport In-Ear Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Earbuds</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sennheiser</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/product_detail_x2_desktop_CX-SPORT-Overview-PI-1.jpg?v=1559061057"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sennheiser<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Earbuds<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            129.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Like an athlete who makes every movement seem effortless, Sennheiser’s CX SPORT in-ear wireless headset elegantly balances purposeful design with exceptional audio performance. Lightweight, sweat and splash resistant, the CX SPORT can be worn around or in front of the neck. Four sizes of ear adapters and three sizes of ear fins provide a personalized fit for optimal wearing comfort and excellent passive reduction of external noise. Sennheiser proprietary transducers, designed and engineered in Germany, deliver balanced and detailed sound with dynamic bass capability. Six-hour battery life with fast-charging ability means the CX SPORT will be ready when you are.</p>

<h6>Superior sound</h6>
<p>Whether you use music to power through a high-intensity workout or to maintain an efficient pace, the wireless CX SPORT is made to move you. Sennheiser engineering ensures clear, detailed sound with satisfying bass response. Qualcomm apt-X processing helps the CX SPORT deliver a High Fidelity audio experience wirelessly. Put the right sound in and get more out, every time you train.</p>

<h6>Exceptional fit and comfort</h6>
<p>Enjoy the freedom of wireless sound with uncompromising quality in a comfortable and ultra-lightweight design. Three sizes of ergonomically designed ear fins keep the earphones in place while four sizes of ear tips provide a customized fit. The adjustable neck cable with integrated clothing clip allows the CX SPORT to move with you. Hit the gym or take a run with Sennheiser sound complimenting your workout.</p>

<h6>Easy to use</h6>
<p>Operation is intuitive and effortless thanks to a slick three-button remote for music and call control. Control the volume or find your go-to power anthem without slowing down. Six-hour battery life means the CX SPORT will go the distance with you, and a ten-minute quick charge gets you one hour of playback when you need it fast.</p>

<h6>Sweat - and splash-resistant</h6>
<p>The CX SPORT doesn’t want you to hold back. Move faster, move further, and feel free to turn it up. Made durable and tough with sweat- and splash-resistant materials, the CX SPORT will join you for an early morning run in the rain or a sweat-soaked gym session.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Sennheiser proprietary transducers, designed and engineered in Germany, deliver balanced and detailed sound with dynamic bass capability</li>
<li>Sweat and splash resistant, designed to compliment your workout activities</li>
<li>6 hour battery life from a 1.5 hours charge. A 10-minute quick charge provides an additional 1 hour of battery life making sure the CX SPORT is ready to work out when you are</li>
<li>Bluetooth 4.2 with multi-point connectivity allows pairing with eight (8) devices and simultaneous connection with two (2) devices</li>
<li>A choice of four sizes (XS, S, M, L) of ear adapters and three sizes (S, M, L) of ear fins create a personalized fit for optimal wearing comfort and excellent passive reduction of external noise. Connectivity Technology: Bluetooth 4.2</li>
<li>Frequency Response - 17 – 21,000 Hz , Impedance - 28 Ohm (Passive), 480 Ohm (Active)</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:195</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sennheiser</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Yellow</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Earbuds</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916213723187</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">129.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-695627-CX--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916213657651</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:30:45-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:30:45-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sennheiser-cx-6-00-bt-wireless-in-ear-headphones"/>
    <title>Sennheiser CX 6.00 BT Wireless In-Ear Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Earbuds</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sennheiser</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/product_detail_x2_desktop_Sennheiser_CX_6_00_BT_1.jpg?v=1559061050"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sennheiser<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Earbuds<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            99.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The Sennheiser CX 6.00BT wireless in-ear headset is everything you need to enjoy music and video on the go. A heavy-weight in sound quality yet clad in an ultra-lightweight frame, it offers exceptional fit and comfort. Advanced Bluetooth technology insures this wireless headset delivers the critically acclaimed Sennheiser sound quality. Intuitive operation and multi-device connectivity with up to 6 battery life and a fast charging function mean the CX 6.00BT will make every day listening more pleasurable, anywhere you go.</p>
<h6>Advanced Wireless Technology</h6>
<p>The CX 6.00BT employs Bluetooth 4.2 and Qualcomm apt-X to ensure true Sennheiser sound. Qualcomm apt-X Low Latency circuitry enhances gaming and video viewing by keeping audio transmission perfectly in sync with the visuals. Additionally, the CX 6.00BT has multi-connectivity with up to two devices. Enjoy your audio and video programing to the fullest, with the freedom and flexibility of wireless listening.</p>
<h6>Intuitive Controls</h6>
<p>The CX 6.00BT is a fully equipped headset with advanced features. Convenient multi-connection capability enables pairing with up to two devices simultaneously. Making and taking calls is easy thanks to the integrated microphone and 3-way calling support. The three-button remote provides control for your music and calls. Convenient voice prompts notify you of incoming calls and battery status.</p>
<h6>Maximum Portability</h6>
<p>The CX 6.00BT is ideal for the music enthusiasts with a mobile lifestyle. A six-hour battery life with fast charging option via USB provides two hours charge in just ten minutes! After only 1.5 hours the CX 6.00BT is fully charged and ready to hit the streets.</p>
<h6>Secure and Comfortable Fit</h6>
<p>The CX 6.00BT is an around-the-neck cable design. This, coupled with angled ergonomic earpieces help ensure they stay in place. To personalize fit for wearing comfort and optimum sound quality, the CX 6.00BT comes with four sizes of silicon ear adaptors (XS, S, M, L). This also contributes to improved attenuation of ambient noise, enhancing listening enjoyment.</p>
<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Bluetooth 4.2 featuring Qualcomm aptX and Qualcomm aptX Low Latency deliver superior sound quality for both music and movies with minimum delay between audio and video</li>
<li>Convenient multi-connection with up to 2 devices simultaneously (phones and computers) with 3-way calling support</li>
<li>6-hour battery life with 1.5 hour fast USB charging</li>
<li>Personalized fit in the ear canals for excellent attenuation of ambient noise (S, M, L and XL ear adapters included)</li>
<li>Two-year warranty when purchased from an authorized Sennheiser dealer</li>
<li>Frequency Response - 17-21,000 Hz , Impedance - 28 Ohm (Passive), 480 Ohm (Active)</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__label2:Our Selection</s:tag>
    <s:tag>__stock:256</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sennheiser</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Blue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Earbuds</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$0 to $100</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916213657651</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">99.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-125033-CX--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204351539</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:21-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:21-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-se-ms7bt-k-high-resolution-compatible-dynamic-sealed-bluetooth-headphones"/>
    <title>Pioneer SE-MS7BT-K High Resolution Compatible Dynamic Sealed Bluetooth Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/339e2b31ad176cc2ee3aaaadfa53c82f_ac27a66e-ead7-4bf1-a7f4-f2ffa30cefc7.jpg?v=1559060544"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            129.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Hi-Res Audio headphones with Bluetooth® capability; the SE-MS7BT offers both wireless &amp; wired headphone solutions and are designed to fit comfortably around the ear for all day listening.</p>

<p>To ensure that you are getting the best sound, the SE-MS7BT supports Qualcomm® aptXTM audio and AAC for high quality audio. By having NFC built-in, this makes it simple to pair another device by simply touching the devices together. The SE-MS7BT headphones utilize Hi-Res capable large 40mm drivers that are fitted perfectly to the wide cushioned ear cups. The SE-MS7BT has controls built into the headphones. But don’t panic when the SE-MS7BT battery runs down, Pioneer has you covered with the included wired cable that allows you to continue listening. The SE-MS7BT are available, in Black, Silver and Tan.</p>

<h6>Enjoy wireless music and calls with the ease of Bluetooth</h6>
<p>Manage music and phone calls using the built in controls and microphone. Simplify the pairing process by using NFC, and listen to high quality audio by using aptX. The built-in battery supports up to 12 hours of continuous use, and when the battery runs down, you can use the included headphone cable to continue listening to music in Hi-Res quality.</p>

<h6>Large 40mm drivers for clear high quality audio</h6>
<p>With the utilization of powerful magnets, the 40 mm driver produces ample lows and the light weight CCAW voice coil reproduces Hi-Res frequencies for enjoyment of Hi-Res audio (the SE-MS7BT requires using the included headphone cable to enjoy Hi-Res audio)</p>

<h6>Wide cushioned headband earpads</h6>
<p>Attention to details was made when designing the headband and earpads. With the design of a wide headband, the weight gets distributed to a larger area by dispersing weight evenly. The earpads are designed to fit a variety of head shapes along with the design of the curve behind the ear to be ergonomic so it creates an even seal all around the ear for a good fit.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Bluetooth® Wireless for Music and Calling</li>
<li>Up to 12 hours Battery Life (rechargeable)</li>
<li>Lightweight &amp; Comfortable</li>
<li>Use NFC for simple device pairing</li>
<li>High Resolution Audio capable</li>
<li>Supports high-fidelity audio CODEC AAC / aptX (connected bluetooth device will also need to support aptX and AAC codecs)</li>
<li>High-resolution capable when used with included headphone cable</li>
<li>NFC (Near Field Communication) one-touch connection</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__label1:New</s:tag>
    <s:tag>__stock:220</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Silver</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204351539</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">129.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-804354-SE--BL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204351539</id>
      <title>Silver</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">129.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-254328-SLI-SI</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203892787</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:13-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:13-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-high-performance-hi-res-balanced-wired-in-ear-headphones-se-ch5blk"/>
    <title>Pioneer High Performance Hi-Res Balanced Wired In-Ear Headphones SE-CH5BL(K)</title>
    <s:type>Earbuds</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/16892_375__1_20de2da5-237a-4403-b3c5-7b3584ef76ab.jpg?v=1559060536"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Earbuds<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            39.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Take a sonic leap forward with the SE-CH5BL, high-performance headphones featuring a 2.5 mm (2/16-inch) stereo connector for Balanced Audio Output. Similar to XLR outputs on flagship hi-fi separates, signals for left and right channels are sent through discrete cables, eliminating noise and crosstalk, lifting headroom, and providing an immersive soundstage thanks to excellent stereo separation.</p>

<p>The SE-CH5BL headphone brings out the best in Hi-Res Audio with ultra-wide-range dynamic drivers reproducing a more complete musical picture. Airflow Control Port preserves mid-range clarity, and bassheads will love the agile low-end performance.</p>

<p>An affordable partner for balanced audio-ready Digital Audio Players, the SE-CH5BL unlocks premium listening wherever your day takes you.</p>

<h6>Balanced Audio Output</h6>
<p>Formerly restricted to desktop headphone setups, balanced audio goes mobile with a new 2.5 mm (2/16-inch) 4-pole plug with discrete braided cables for L/R channels. Music expands into the headroom this technology provides as noise vanishes and details come into clearer focus.</p>

<h6>Airflow Control Port</h6>
<p>This exclusive Pioneer technology was developed to clarify the middle bandwidth occupied by the voice. It works by improving separation between mid and bass frequencies. Enjoy clarity uncommon to headphones at this price-point.</p>

<h6>Over-the-Ear Cable Design</h6>
<p>As well as providing a comfortable and secure fit, the over-the-ear cable design reduces cable-borne interference that occurs with conventional headphones. Fewer bumps on the cable as you walk let you enjoy music, not noise. The SE-CH5BL-K has a high quality tangle-resistant cable with gold-plated headphone jack assures high fidelity reproduction with minimal touch noise.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Hi-Res playback from large 9.7mm driver</li>
<li>Acoustic port to reproduce a low and mid frequency clear sound</li>
<li>Enjoy clear, precise, dynamic sound with a balanced Connection</li>
<li>Touch noise reduced by over-ear fit style</li>
<li>Silicone tips with ribs in 3 sizes (S, M, L) to ensure comfortable fit - includes carrying pouch</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:179</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Earbuds</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$0 to $100</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203892787</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-841061-HIG-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916202975283</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:21:49-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:21:49-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/master-dynamic-mw60-wireless-over-ear-headphones"/>
    <title>Master Dynamic MW60 Wireless Over-Ear Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Master &amp; Dynamic</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/2714e34d94372f824fe0a4ade01e3e8f.jpg?v=1559060512"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Master &amp; Dynamic<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            549.00 - 608.00
            <a href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/master-dynamic-mw60-wireless-over-ear-headphones">(4 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The MW60 is a top of the line award winning wireless headphone. High performance 45mm neodymium drivers and a signal range 4x industry standard with a 16 hour battery life combine for the highest performance. Premium leather, patent pending stainless steel components and a 'form-meets-function' exposed all-aluminum antenna, come together to create uncompromised durability, style and best-in-class signal range.</p>

<p>The MW60 Wireless Over Ear Headphones have the perfect balance of aesthetics, strength, comfort and sound and are engineered to last.</p>

<h6>Designed for Decades of Use</h6>
<p>The MW60 features the highest performance technical features. These include a 45mm Neodymium driver to deliver the best sound quality, Bluetooth 4.1 with Aptx and our patent pending aluminum antenna for unparalleled connectivity.</p>

<h6>Appointed with the Finest Materials</h6>
<p>We build our products using only the finest and most durable luxury materials, maintaining the perfect balance of aesthetics, strength, comfort and utility. Engineered to last using premium leather, lambskin memory foam ear pads and stainless details.</p>

<h6>Tuned for a Rich, Warm Sound</h6>
<p>We sought a natural, detailed, live sound signature for our headphones. Our expansive soundscape captures the detail that well recorded music has to offer. Our tuning was designed to complement a diversity of tastes and musical genres.</p>

<h6>Complemented by Functional Details</h6>
<p>We carefully crafted essential functions and practical details into our designs, from the easily replaceable parts, to separating the microphone from the remote for increased vocal clarity. These details ensure that in addition to the high quality sound and design, they are comfortable and easy to use.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<p>Technical features including a 3x industry average Bluetooth signal range and a 16-hour rechargeable battery combine with premium materials, a minimal industrial aesthetic and our signature rich, warm sound.</p>
<ul>
<li>Heavy Grain Premium Leather: Heavy grain premium cowhide on headband exterior surface and ear cup accents, soft lambskin on headband interior and ear pads.</li>
<li>Omni-Directional Dual Microphone: Noise-isolating microphone to provide greater clarity.</li>
<li>Tactile Controls: Intuitive controls similar to those found in elegant timepieces.</li>
<li>Genuine Lambskin Ear Pads: Memory foam, wrapped in lambskin, providing superior comfort and breathability, removable for cleaning.</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:254</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Master &amp; Dynamic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$500 to $800</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916202975283</id>
      <title>Black / No</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">549.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAS-240534-DYN-BL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916202975283</id>
      <title>Black / Yes</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">608.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAS-959112-DYN-BL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916202975283</id>
      <title>Brown/Silver / Yes</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">608.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-326792-ELI-BR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916202975283</id>
      <title>Brown/Silver / No</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">608.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-326792-ELI-BR</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
