<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/collections/pioneer.atom"/>
  <title>Warehouse - Metal</title>
  <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:52-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Warehouse - Metal</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916205432883</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:52-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:52-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-vsx-lx301-7-2-channel-networked-av-receiver-with-built-in-bluetooth-and-wi-fi"/>
    <title>Pioneer VSX-LX301 7.2-Ch Networked A/V Receiver with Built-In Bluetooth and Wi-Fi</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/cf527b1ec9b2c638ad84b561b487f4be_faee3599-f41d-403d-82ba-d75090c777c5.jpg?v=1559060574"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            700.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The VSX-LX301 features Dolby Atmos and DTS:X audio formats for fully-immersive surround sound. Connect to all your favorite music sources with support for the latest Dual Band Wi-Fi network connections to stream Google Cast, TuneIn, Deezer, and Tidal. The new 384kHz/32 bit DAC provides superior playback of all music resolutions from MP3s to Hi-Res audio files. Support for multi-room audio allows sources connected to the AV receiver to be played back in different rooms.</p>

<p>Google Cast, TIDAL, and Deezer require future firmware update. Deezer currently not available in US.</p>

<h6>DTS:X Ready</h6>
<p>DTS:X leverages object-based audio to enable immersive audio experiences. It automatically adapts audio to the existing channels and speaker system, so no specific speaker layout is required. Experience a soundscape with incredibly rich and life-like audio.</p>

<h6>General Specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>170 W/ch (6 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 0.9 %, 1ch Driven FTC)</li>
<li>100 W/ch (8 ohms, 20 Hz-20 kHz, THD 0.08 %, 2ch Driven FTC)</li>
<li>Ultra HD Pass-through with HDCP 2.2</li>
<li>Built-in Wi-Fi and Bluetooth</li>
<li>MCACC Auto Room Tuning</li>
<li>Dolby Atmos</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:280</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$500 to $800</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916205432883</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">700.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SAM-864377-43--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916205334579</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:44-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:44-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-vsx-lx103-elite-7-2-channel-network-a-v-receiver"/>
    <title>Pioneer VSX-LX103 Elite 7.2-Ch Network A/V Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/81fod-rsyyl._sl1500_46c1b819-d339-4aba-9a33-eeb06728b916.jpg?v=1559060570"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            499.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Featuring 5.2.2ch surround sound with Dolby Atmos and DTS:X optimized by MCACC, and spectacular view by Ultra HD video, HDR10, HLG, and Dolby Vision, the VSX-LX103 brings the thrills of the movie theater to your home. What's more, Flare Connect offers wireless multi-room audio with easy control on the Pioneer Remote App for various sources including vinyl records. Songs from internet radio and network streaming services can also be enjoyed with Chromecast built-in and DTS Play-Fi via your smartphone.</p>

<h6>Works with Sonos</h6>
<p>The awesome home theater you’ve built around your Elite receiver can now be part of your existing Sonos Home Sound System, or the start of a new one.</p>
<p>After a simple set up, your Elite A/V receiver will seamlessly tie into Sonos, instantly waking, changing inputs and playing at the volume you command through the familiar Sonos app.</p>

<h6>Dolby Atmos/Dolby Surround Upmixing</h6>
<p>Reproduce object-oriented sound in smooth, curving movements, or the realistic three-dimensional movement overhead by the top speakers. Other audio codecs including DTS formats can be upmixed using Dolby Surround for enjoying 3D surround sound.</p>

<h6>Next Generation Video Standard Ready</h6>
<p>All HDMI terminals support 4K (60p/4:4:4/24-bit), Wide Color Gamut (BT.2020), and HDCP 2.2, so you will have no problem when upgrading to new devices.</p>

<h6>Chromecast built-in</h6>
<p>Control audio from anywhere in the house using Chromecast enabled apps running on your personal device. The VSX-LX103 also works with the Google Assistant, so you can give voice commands via Google Assistant built-in devices such as Google Home to operate the AV receiver without lifting a finger.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Direct energy amplification at 170 W/Ch (6 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 10 %, 1Ch Driven)/ 80 W/Ch (8 ohms, 20 Hz-20 kHz, THD 0.08 %, 2Ch Driven, FTC)</li>
<li>4K Ultra HD pass-through with HDCP 2.2, Dolby vision compatible with HDR10, hlg and BT.2020 support (4K/60p/4: 4: 4/24-bit) and 1080p to 4K upscaling</li>
<li>Your Pioneer receiver can now be part of your existing Sonos Home Sound System, or the start of a new one. Instantly upgrade the music streaming capability of your home theater receiver with Sonos Connect and a free firmware update.</li>
<li>Ready for surround sound tracks with Dolby Atmos, Dolby Surround Upmixer, DTS:X, DTS Neural:X Upmixer and more</li>
<li>Multi-room audio with Chromecast built-in, DTS Play-Fi and Flare Connect</li>
<li>Music, Pandora, Spotify, Tidal, and Deezer music-streaming services ready and tune in internet radio</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:192</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916205334579</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">499.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-587425-VSX-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916205137971</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:40-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:40-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-sw-8mk2-andrew-jones-designed-100-watt-powered-subwoofer"/>
    <title>Pioneer SW-8MK2 Andrew Jones Designed 100-Watt Powered Subwoofer</title>
    <s:type>Subwoofers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/81HrrDOLEwL._SL1500.jpg?v=1559060563"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Subwoofers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            159.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Looking for an affordable, low-distortion way to get down deep into the low end of the audio spectrum? The Pioneer SW-8MK2 subwoofer will meet with your thunderous approval. Nothing in this price category gives you a deeper appreciation for quality bass like the new SW-8MK2 Subwoofer from Pioneer. Fire up your favorite movie, then buckle up, sit back, and let its powerful 100 watt amplifier bring you right into the experience with room-shaking, earth-quaking realism. Its vented enclosure means extended deep, clean, bass performance. Phase and frequency controls allow for customized set-up. High- and low-level inputs mean flexible installation.</p>

<h6>70 Years of Audio Firsts</h6>
<p>This subwoofer comes with a remarkable pedigree of over 70 years of Pioneer audio heritage and industry firsts. Like every subwoofer Pioneer builds, the SW-8MK2 is engineered to offer incredible design and amazing low-end frequency sound quality. The Pioneer SW-8MK2 Subwoofer offers extraordinary performance and remarkable quality to deliver a phenomenal music and home theater experience.</p>

<h6>Brillant Sound from a Brilliant Design</h6>
<p>The 8-inch long-throw woofer is powered by a 100 watt amplifier for earth-shaking detail in your favorite movies and music. A vented enclosure allows for extended, well-rounded bass.</p>

<h6>Customize Your Sound</h6>
<p>Use the phase adjustment and crossover adjustment controls to fine-tune the sound for your particular room. Whether your room is big or small, or you primarily listen to music or watch TV and movies with the whole family, the Pioneer SW-8MK2 Subwoofer delivers the low-end that makes everyone sit up and pay attention.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Powerful 100 Watt internal amplifier for controlled bass at any volume level high or low ; Maximum Input Power 100 W</li>
<li>8” long throw woofer allows for lower frequencies than traditional woofers ; Dimensions (W x H x D) 12-3/16” x 14-3/16” x 12-3/16”</li>
<li>Crossover and Phase Adjustments to perfectly blend subwoofer with your speakers ; Power Requirement.120 V/60Hz</li>
<li>Frequency Range: 38 Hz – 150 Hz ;Power Consumption 1.0A</li>
<li>Speaker level and line level inputs for installation options using either speaker wire or a subwoofer cable</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:281</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Subwoofers</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916205137971</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">159.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-873362-VSX-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204908595</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:34-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:34-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-sp-bs22-lr-andrew-jones-designed-bookshelf-loudspeakers"/>
    <title>Pioneer SP-BS22-LR Andrew Jones Designed Bookshelf Loudspeakers</title>
    <s:type>Speakers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/91xvXHh1i7L._SL1500.jpg?v=1559060559"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Speakers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            129.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>High quality home audio doesn't have to break the bank. As proof, Pioneer introduces the SP-BS22-LR bookshelf speakers. Whether you use them as stereo speakers or part of a multi-channel home theater system, their ability to handle 90 watts the SP-BS22-LR's deliver wide frequency response and sophisticated sound quality regardless of the source.</p><p>Whatever your system, the SP-BS22-LR Bookshelf Speakers are ready to step it up with authentic audio reproduction to bring your listening experience to the next level.</p>

<h6>70 Years of Audio Firsts</h6>
<p>These speakers come with a remarkable pedigree of over 70 years of Pioneer audio heritage and industry firsts. Like every speaker Pioneer builds, these are engineered to offer incredible design and amazing sound quality. Pioneer has brought their high-end expertise and passion to the creation of this affordable bookshelf speaker.</p>

<h6>Thinking Out Of the Box</h6>
<p>Typically you'll find most bookshelf speakers not only come in a box, they are a box. And while that might be better for production costs, it isn't better for sound reproduction. The SP-BS22-LR speakers utilize a true curved cabinet design. So besides the aesthetics being considerably more pleasing, this stiffer design reduces standing sound waves inside the cabinet, resulting in high-performance and exceptional sound quality.</p>

<p>As you look at them, you'll also notice the unique speaker grills. They're beautiful and elegant in their own right, but not for their own sake. They protect the speakers, but are also removable if you prefer to see the drivers themselves.</p>

<h6>The Inside Story</h6>
<em>Crossover</em>
<p>The job of the crossover in a speaker is to break the audio signal into low, high, and sometimes mid-range frequencies. It's an important job, and it uses circuitry like inductors and capacitors to accomplish it. Most speakers use an extremely simple, low-cost crossover made up of a single capacitor and inductor. The Pioneer SP-BS22-LR utilizes a sophisticated 6-element, high-quality crossover. The reasoning is simple: because it's one more way of ensuring high quality sound that makes its presence known.</p>

<em>Woofer</em>
<p>In the SP-BS22-LR, Pioneer has added a structured surface to the 4-inch woofer. By doing so, not only is rigidity improved, so is bass accuracy. Engineers have also vented the pole piece, improving bass response from the same size woofers in previous models.</p>

<em>Tweeter</em>
<p>To widen the sweet spot of the 1-inch High Efficiency Soft Dome tweeter, Pioneer has engineered a custom wave guide. Increasing tweeter efficiency, together with newly designed crossovers, allows the SP-BS22-LR's play louder using less power.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>80 Watt Power Handling, Nominal Impedance 6 ohms</li>
<li>RF Molded Curved Cabinets to reduce internal standing waves</li>
<li>4 inches Structured Surface Woofer with oversized magnets and vented pole piece for improved bass response</li>
<li>1 inch High Efficiency Soft Dome Tweeter for smooth high frequency reproduction even at high volume levels</li>
<li>6 Element Complex Crossover perfectly blends audio between the woofer and tweeter for greater accuracy</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:65</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Speakers</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204908595</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">129.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-407861-SW--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204613683</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:27-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:27-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-slim-audio-video-component-receiver-vsx-s520"/>
    <title>Pioneer Slim Audio &amp; Video Component Receiver Black (VSX-S520)</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/12973_849__2_af411f77-6937-4c5a-a2e9-11e9dbbf4221.jpg?v=1559060553"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            399.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Bringing quality sound and the latest Features in a slim and stylish design, thanks to a highly-efficient class D amplifier. Enjoy spectacular images with Ultra HD (4K/60p/4:4:4) upscale/pass-through, play Hi-Res audio via USB/network, listen to internet radio and various streaming services, or cast music with chrome cast built-in. The slim, stylish design and efficient power makes the VSX-S520 an ideal addition to any home Cinema, It is 120v.</p>

<h6>Built-in Dual Band Wi-Fi</h6>
<p>Enjoy network features such as audio streaming via wireless LAN connection. The built-in Wi-Fi is dual band, supporting both 5 GHz and 2.4 GHz frequency channels. By using the 5 GHz band, you can enjoy steady and uninterrupted streaming of audio files.</p>

<h6>Ultra HD Upscaling/Pass-Through with HDCP 2.2</h6>
<p>The feature lets you take advantage of the highest-quality video source for viewing on a 4K TV. With support for HDCP 2.2, you can enjoy premium content such as 4K videos with digital copy protection on a compatible display.</p>

<h6>Next Generation Video Standard Ready</h6>
<p>The VSX-S520 is ready for the next generation video standard HDR (High Dynamic Range) and BT.2020, which were adopted by Ultra HD Blu-ray. HDR is a technology that drastically expands the brightness peak, providing a higher contrast between light and dark images, which creates even more life-like pictures. BT.2020 is a new color-recording technology allowing a much wider gamut than the current BT.709 standard, enabling vividly rich coloration.</p>

<h6>MCACC Auto Room Tuning</h6>
<p>Create the optimum acoustic environment with Pioneer’s MCACC (Multi-Channel Acoustic Calibration System), developed with the expertise of professional recording studios. With the custom microphone, the system automatically compensates for differences in speaker size, level and distance, and equalizes response. As an innovative solution for the phase lag between the subwoofer and the main channel speakers caused by the network filter, Phase Control compensates the delayed bass to improve sound synchronization.</p>

<h6>Multi-room Audio Offers a Variety of Ways to Enjoy Music</h6>
<p>The VSX-S520 will support FireConnect Powered by Blackfire with a future firmware update. FireConnect is a stable wireless protocol that streams audio from a compatible Pioneer AV Receiver to a compatible Pioneer wireless speaker. Enjoy Bluetooth audio, front USB audio files and internet radio from the FireConnect compatible Pioneer AV receiver to an optional FireConnect compatible Pioneer wireless speaker(s) located in another room(s).</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Slim, 2.76” low-profile design 5.1 Ch network A/V receiver featuring MCACC room calibration. Dolby Atoms: 3.1.2Ch</li>
<li>Ultra HD pass-through (4K UltraHD 60p/4: 4: 4/HDR.10/BT.2020) with HDCP 2.2 and 4K upscaling (1080p to 4K)</li>
<li>Highly-efficient class D amplifier driving 80 W/Ch (4 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 1.0 %, 1Ch Driven FTC); 50 W/Ch (4 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 1.0 %, 2Ch Driven FTC)</li>
<li>Music file playback: MP3, WMA, AAC, Apple lossless, WAV, FLAC, AIFF, DSD via USB and network (Up to 192kHz/24-bit). sound delay (Lip Sync): 500 ms at 48K/ 400 ms at 96K/ 200 ms at 192K</li>
<li>Enjoy limitless streams of your favorite online music and internet radio stations including Spotify and for the first time tune in, Tidal, and Deeper</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:245</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204613683</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">399.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-108512-SLI-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204351539</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:21-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:21-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-se-ms7bt-k-high-resolution-compatible-dynamic-sealed-bluetooth-headphones"/>
    <title>Pioneer SE-MS7BT-K High Resolution Compatible Dynamic Sealed Bluetooth Headphones</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/339e2b31ad176cc2ee3aaaadfa53c82f_ac27a66e-ead7-4bf1-a7f4-f2ffa30cefc7.jpg?v=1559060544"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            129.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Hi-Res Audio headphones with Bluetooth® capability; the SE-MS7BT offers both wireless &amp; wired headphone solutions and are designed to fit comfortably around the ear for all day listening.</p>

<p>To ensure that you are getting the best sound, the SE-MS7BT supports Qualcomm® aptXTM audio and AAC for high quality audio. By having NFC built-in, this makes it simple to pair another device by simply touching the devices together. The SE-MS7BT headphones utilize Hi-Res capable large 40mm drivers that are fitted perfectly to the wide cushioned ear cups. The SE-MS7BT has controls built into the headphones. But don’t panic when the SE-MS7BT battery runs down, Pioneer has you covered with the included wired cable that allows you to continue listening. The SE-MS7BT are available, in Black, Silver and Tan.</p>

<h6>Enjoy wireless music and calls with the ease of Bluetooth</h6>
<p>Manage music and phone calls using the built in controls and microphone. Simplify the pairing process by using NFC, and listen to high quality audio by using aptX. The built-in battery supports up to 12 hours of continuous use, and when the battery runs down, you can use the included headphone cable to continue listening to music in Hi-Res quality.</p>

<h6>Large 40mm drivers for clear high quality audio</h6>
<p>With the utilization of powerful magnets, the 40 mm driver produces ample lows and the light weight CCAW voice coil reproduces Hi-Res frequencies for enjoyment of Hi-Res audio (the SE-MS7BT requires using the included headphone cable to enjoy Hi-Res audio)</p>

<h6>Wide cushioned headband earpads</h6>
<p>Attention to details was made when designing the headband and earpads. With the design of a wide headband, the weight gets distributed to a larger area by dispersing weight evenly. The earpads are designed to fit a variety of head shapes along with the design of the curve behind the ear to be ergonomic so it creates an even seal all around the ear for a good fit.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Bluetooth® Wireless for Music and Calling</li>
<li>Up to 12 hours Battery Life (rechargeable)</li>
<li>Lightweight &amp; Comfortable</li>
<li>Use NFC for simple device pairing</li>
<li>High Resolution Audio capable</li>
<li>Supports high-fidelity audio CODEC AAC / aptX (connected bluetooth device will also need to support aptX and AAC codecs)</li>
<li>High-resolution capable when used with included headphone cable</li>
<li>NFC (Near Field Communication) one-touch connection</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__label1:New</s:tag>
    <s:tag>__stock:220</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Silver</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204351539</id>
      <title>Black</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">129.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-804354-SE--BL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204351539</id>
      <title>Silver</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">129.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-254328-SLI-SI</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204187699</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:17-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:17-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-pl-990-automatic-stereo-turntable"/>
    <title>Pioneer PL-990 Automatic Stereo Turntable</title>
    <s:type>Turntables</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/11337_041__1_2371cb96-e9a6-41e3-a153-5fe90ebf0744.jpg?v=1559060540"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Turntables<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            179.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The PL-990 is a fully automatic turntable with a built-in phono equalizer that has the ability to connect directly to a line or auxiliary input. It also includes a moving magnet cartridge that has a diamond stylus.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Two speeds so you can play LPs and 45s</li>
<li>Fully automatic operation means you push a single button to play a record and the unit automatically suts itself off</li>
<li>Low-mass straight tone arm: Highly sensitive and resistant to resonance, track records better</li>
<li>Universal-type cartridge connector</li>
<li>Moving magnet cartridge included</li>
<li>Built-in phono Equalizer - Simply connect to any auxilliary/line Input on your amplifier or mini Audio system</li>
<li>P-mount cartridge</li>
<li>Low-vibration, belt-drive design</li>
<li>Rubber platter mat</li>
<li>Vibration-absorbing feet</li>
<li>Hinged dust cover</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__label1:New</s:tag>
    <s:tag>__stock:262</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Turntables</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204187699</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">179.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-987561-SE--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203892787</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:13-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:13-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-high-performance-hi-res-balanced-wired-in-ear-headphones-se-ch5blk"/>
    <title>Pioneer High Performance Hi-Res Balanced Wired In-Ear Headphones SE-CH5BL(K)</title>
    <s:type>Earbuds</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/16892_375__1_20de2da5-237a-4403-b3c5-7b3584ef76ab.jpg?v=1559060536"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Earbuds<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            39.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Take a sonic leap forward with the SE-CH5BL, high-performance headphones featuring a 2.5 mm (2/16-inch) stereo connector for Balanced Audio Output. Similar to XLR outputs on flagship hi-fi separates, signals for left and right channels are sent through discrete cables, eliminating noise and crosstalk, lifting headroom, and providing an immersive soundstage thanks to excellent stereo separation.</p>

<p>The SE-CH5BL headphone brings out the best in Hi-Res Audio with ultra-wide-range dynamic drivers reproducing a more complete musical picture. Airflow Control Port preserves mid-range clarity, and bassheads will love the agile low-end performance.</p>

<p>An affordable partner for balanced audio-ready Digital Audio Players, the SE-CH5BL unlocks premium listening wherever your day takes you.</p>

<h6>Balanced Audio Output</h6>
<p>Formerly restricted to desktop headphone setups, balanced audio goes mobile with a new 2.5 mm (2/16-inch) 4-pole plug with discrete braided cables for L/R channels. Music expands into the headroom this technology provides as noise vanishes and details come into clearer focus.</p>

<h6>Airflow Control Port</h6>
<p>This exclusive Pioneer technology was developed to clarify the middle bandwidth occupied by the voice. It works by improving separation between mid and bass frequencies. Enjoy clarity uncommon to headphones at this price-point.</p>

<h6>Over-the-Ear Cable Design</h6>
<p>As well as providing a comfortable and secure fit, the over-the-ear cable design reduces cable-borne interference that occurs with conventional headphones. Fewer bumps on the cable as you walk let you enjoy music, not noise. The SE-CH5BL-K has a high quality tangle-resistant cable with gold-plated headphone jack assures high fidelity reproduction with minimal touch noise.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Hi-Res playback from large 9.7mm driver</li>
<li>Acoustic port to reproduce a low and mid frequency clear sound</li>
<li>Enjoy clear, precise, dynamic sound with a balanced Connection</li>
<li>Touch noise reduced by over-ear fit style</li>
<li>Silicone tips with ribs in 3 sizes (S, M, L) to ensure comfortable fit - includes carrying pouch</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:179</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Earbuds</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Headphones</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$0 to $100</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203892787</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-841061-HIG-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203696179</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:07-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:07-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-hi-res-digital-audio-player-xdp-300rs"/>
    <title>Pioneer Hi-Res Digital Audio Player XDP-300R(S)</title>
    <s:type>Walkmans</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/14051_165__1_baafaba0-2418-47b0-bf4a-4b9efca03e33.jpg?v=1559060531"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Walkmans<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            699.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Enjoy hi-res audio with the silver XDP-300R Digital Audio Player from Pioneer. This portable player features a 4.7" capacitive touchscreen display that makes navigating through favorite tracks and playlists easy and intuitive. The XDP-300R supports multiple audio formats, including up to 11.2 MHz DSD, 384 kHz/24-bit PCM, FLAC, ALAC, WAV, AIFF, and MQA files. It comes with 32GB of built-in memory and features dual microSD card slots for expanding the base storage even further. The XDP-300R is equipped with both 2.5mm balanced and 3.5mm headphone outputs. It also supports Bluetooth and Wi-Fi technology for streaming audio. Audio can also be played via the micro-USB-B/OTG digital output.</p>
<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>In addition to the DAC and amplifier of the highest class, also equipped with Android OS. Equipped with a high-resolution model / highest level of DAC and amplifier also corresponding to the balance output by two groups, adopting the audio-grade parts. 300R dedicated tuning</li>
<li>Equipped with ESS manufactured by DAC "ES9018K2M" amplifier "SABRE9601K" one by each of the two groups</li>
<li>Corresponds to the most recent "MQA". MQA Limited is corresponding to the reproduction of became the developer "MQA" / â— 2 one of balance drive that you can select according to preference</li>
<li>High Precision EQ-HD / Club Sound Boost</li>
<li>High precision graphic equalizer which can adjust the volume of up to 16,384 band (frequency band)</li>
</ul>
<h6>Playback a Multitude of High Quality Audio Sources</h6>
<p>The XDP-300R supports all your current audio from MP3’s to streaming music from your favorite internet apps. With playback support for up to 11.2MHz DSD, 384kHz/24 bit PCM, FLAC, ALAC, WAV, AIFF, and MQA it is possible to enjoy many existing Hi-Res audio formats. Equipped with both 2.5 mm balanced output and 3.5 mm headphone output; audio can also be output via Micro USB-B/OTG digital output, and wireless output to connect the XDP-300R offers a wide selection of headphones and peripherals. Compatible Formats: DSD(DSF/DSDIFF)/FLAC/ALAC/WAV/AIFF/MQA/OggVorbis/MP3/AAC.</p>
<h6>High Resolution Playback with Twin DAC &amp; Amp Setup</h6>
<p>Incorporating twin unit ESS Technology DAC “ES9018K2M” and AMP “SABRE 9601K” each allows for extreme high resolution audio and component audio design philosophy while still maintaining a realistic power envelop for a portable device.</p>
<h6>Large capacity storage and battery life</h6>
<p>Equipped with 2 micro SD card slots (up to 200GBs each) ,the internal memory of 32GBs (including system area), have access to up to 432GBs of storage for music, movies, and apps. With up to 16 hours of Hi-Res audio playback, play to your heart's content.</p>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:146</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Silver</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$500 to $800</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Walkmans</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203696179</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">699.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-434147-HI--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203401267</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:02-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:02-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-elite-universal-disc-player-udp-lx500"/>
    <title>Pioneer UDP-LX500 Elite Universal Disc Player</title>
    <s:type>Home Cinema</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/UDP-LX500_B__front.jpg?v=1559060525"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Home Cinema<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            999.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Elite’s brand-new universal disc player brings the spectacle of Ultra HD Blu-ray to your home entertainment, with four times the resolution of 1080P Full HD. Featuring three-block internal layout, Ultra rigid construction, and double-layered chassis for a robust build, 6-layered main circuit board, SDR/HDR preset mode, and support for HDR10/Dolby vision for quality picture, as well as premium audio DAC and zero signal terminal for high-grade sound, The UDP-LX500 lets you enjoy the highest video resolution as well as your other digital disc collections.</p>

<h6>Ultra HD Blu-ray Playback</h6>
<p>Certified by the UHD Alliance, the new Elite UDP-LX500 meets or exceeds strict performance specifications for resolution (4K – 4 times sharper than HD), high dynamic range (HDR – brilliant brights, deepest darks), and wide color spectrum (more lifelike colors). It also focuses on other video and audio attributes including immersive audio (multi-dimensional sound) among others.</p>

<h6>Three-Block Internal Layout</h6>
<p>The blocks for power supply, drive/digital processing, and analog audio are separated into three to eliminate electrical and magnetic interference between the blocks.</p>

<h6>6-Layered Main Circuit Board for High S/N Ratio</h6>
<p>A 6-layered IVH is used for the main circuit board to thoroughly eliminate digital noise. This optimizes the digital signal wiring and minimises GND impedance, and dramatically improves S/N ratio in audio/video signal processing. The 18 Gbps transmission through the latest HDMI standard becomes even more precise.</p>

<h6>PQLS Jitter-less Sound Transmission</h6>
<p>With the precision quartz controller on a compatible AV receiver, Pioneer’s PQLS (Precision Quartz Lock System) eliminates distortion caused by timing errors.</p>

<p>It controls the amount of audio signals from the AV receiver to the UDP-LX500, giving the best possible digital-to-analog conversion. UDP-LX500 supports PQLS 2ch Audio, Multi-Surround, and Bit-stream.</p>

<h6>Zero Signal Terminal</h6>
<p>The Zero Signal Terminal is a Pioneer-original feature dedicated to tuning audio and video quality without signal transmission. By connecting the Zero Signal Terminal with the audio/video input terminal of an AV receiver etc., the reference level (GND) of the audio/video signals is aligned between the two devices, and the potential difference is suppressed, allowing a precise and high-quality signal transmission.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Ultra HD Blu-ray playback</li>
<li>Three-block internal layout (power supply, drive/Digital processing, analog audio)</li>
<li>6-Layered main circuit board for high S/N Ratio</li>
<li>PQLS jitter-less sound transmission</li>
<li>Elite products are backed by a three-year parts and labor warranty</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
<li>
</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:115</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Blu-Ray &amp; DVD Players</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$800 to $1500</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203401267</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">999.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-204397-ELI-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203171891</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:21:57-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:21:57-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-elite-slim-receiver-audio-video-component-receiver-sx-s30"/>
    <title>Pioneer SX-S30 Elite Slim Receiver Audio &amp; Video Component Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13120_704__1_e925be8b-8a59-4b3f-a872-ef8d8cce230d.jpg?v=1559060521"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            449.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>With the Pioneer Elite SX-S30 you can enjoy various audio entertainment including Hi-Res audio files, music streaming services, internet radio, CDs, and vinyl records. Being equipped with Bluetooth wireless technology, airplay, and built-in Wi-Fi, you can wirelessly stream songs. With the built in Class-D amplification and thin design, this network receiver can fit in small places. If you have a streaming device, you can listen to songs by plugging them to the HDMI terminal. Just connect the speaker of your choice, and play and listen the way you like.</p>

<h6>Hi-Res Audio File Playback via USB/Network</h6>
<p>You can play up to 5.6 MHz DSD (Direct Stream Digital) files, and up to 192 kHz/24-bit WAV, FLAC, AIFF, and Apple Lossless files from a USB device or via wired or wireless network.</p>

<h6>Versatile Connectivity</h6>
<p>The SX-S30 is equipped with the phono (MM) input for a vinyl record player, as well as optical and coaxial digital inputs for connecting other audio sources. The HDMI (HDCP 2.2) terminal lets you connect to your streaming devices’ and enjoy audio streaming.</p>

<h6>Connect with AirPlay and Wi-Fi</h6>
<p>After connecting your SX-S30 to your home network, you can control/access your music library with the remote control, or play music from your phone or tablet using AirPlay.</p>

<h6>Wireless Multi-room Audio</h6>
<p>The SX-S30 will support FireConnect Powered by Blackfire with a future firmware update. FireConnect is a stable wireless protocol that streams audio from a compatible Pioneer Receiver to a compatible Pioneer wireless speaker x 2. Enjoy Bluetooth audio, front USB audio files and internet radio from the FireConnect compatible Pioneer receiver to an optional FireConnect compatible Pioneer wireless speaker(s) located in another room(s).</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>5 W/Ch (4 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 1.0 %, 1Ch Driven) 2-ch network receiver with Class-D amplification</li>
<li>Built-in Bluetooth and Wi-Fi (dual band 5 GHz/2.4 GHz). Apple airplay Certified with Pandora, Spotify, Tidal, and Deezer music streaming services ready</li>
<li>HDMI 4 in/1 out (HDCP 2.2)</li>
<li>Hi-Res Audio file playback via USB/network and phono (mm) input for a vinyl record player</li>
<li>Chromecast built-in and DTS Play-Fi technology (via future firmware updates)</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__label1:New</s:tag>
    <s:tag>__stock:108</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203171891</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">449.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-450969-ELI-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
