<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/collections/professional-audio.atom"/>
  <title>Warehouse - Metal</title>
  <updated>2019-05-28T12:41:27-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Warehouse - Metal</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916224012339</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:41:27-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:41:27-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/yamaha-ns-sw300-subwoofer"/>
    <title>Yamaha NS-SW300 Subwoofer</title>
    <s:type>Subwoofers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Yamaha</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/2c05017e693ad594772a02d9ce682099.jpg?v=1559061690"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Yamaha<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Subwoofers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            499.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>A design combining superior operability and beauty. And introducing a new technology, Twisted Flare Port, for clear and tight bass. A subwoofer that will match a wide range of speakers and interiors.</p>
<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>PWM digital drive high efficiency amplifier and dual feedback circuit</li>
<li>New Twisted Flare Port contributes to clear and tight bass</li>
<li>Advanced YST II (Yamaha Active Servo Technology II)</li>
<li>25 cm (10”) cone woofer with square wire voice coil</li>
<li>Beautiful design will match a wide range of speakers and interiors</li>
<li>Front control panel for easy control</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:172</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Yamaha</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Subwoofers</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916224012339</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">499.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>YAM-970216-NS-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916223160371</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:40:41-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:40:41-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/yamaha-a-s3000-natural-sound-integrated-amplifier"/>
    <title>Yamaha A-S3000 Natural Sound Integrated Amplifier</title>
    <s:type>Amplifiers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Yamaha</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/67E0B30443FB4D82BACC24E85032C37D_12073_3022x1467_d7336515811f8b83d420f265d2aa87e2_9debdd33-d911-4087-b2f6-bee11354dcc0.jpg?v=1559061648"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Yamaha<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Amplifiers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            6999.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>A piano comes into this world through the perfect synergy of advanced technical skill and artistry. Such a piano can create sound that truly reflects the player's feelings. The final stage in piano production is called “voicing.” This breathes life into the instrument and truly makes it musical. To accomplish this, highly skilled experts focus their concentration and sensitivity completely on each note and delicately adjust the hardness and resilience of the hammers that strike the strings, establishing the perfect, consistent sound for the entire instrument and determining its tonal personality.</p>
<p>Yamaha brings this exact same approach and process to its audio products. Our experienced technicians perform exhaustive listening tests and strictly consider every single element and component, to draw closer — step by meticulous step — to the ideal sound. Introducing the S3000 Series, the absolute culmination of hi-fidelity audio. Yamaha knows all about sound and even more about music, and has brought all its rich artistic sensitivity into the creation of this line.</p>
<p>All the energy and finely nuanced technique of the artist, all the power and subtlety of the original music is fully reproduced, with absolutely nothing left out. The result is a remarkably pure sound—powerfully expressive and exquisitely profound. Beautiful and elegant in appearance, sturdy and reliable in construction, created with the latest, innovative technology and genuine craftsmanship—all nurtured by our long experience in the manufacture of musical instruments. Yamaha proudly offers this new high-end lineup, delivering supreme quality in every way. This is the manifestation of our passion to give music lovers the ultimate in listening enjoyment—a tradition we've been carrying on and advancing for more than 125 years.</p>
<h6>A-S3000</h6>
<p>Profoundly accurate sound with the full expressive power of the music. Exceptional sonic purity, elimination of signal loss — in an exquisite, elegant design.The supreme culmination of the Yamaha line — the A-S3000.</p>
<ul>
<li>Rigid Streamlined Construction: provides strict anti-vibration protection, and enables shortest cabling routes</li>
<li>Large toroidal transformer, solidly mounted with independent three-dimensional inner frame</li>
<li>Comprehensive low impedance design, shortened signal paths and copper-plated chassis</li>
<li>Six mm thick top panel made of non-magnetic aluminium plate</li>
<li>Left-right symmetrical design for independent pre amp and power amp blocks</li>
<li>Floating and Balanced Power Amplifier with MOSFETs</li>
<li>All-stage balanced transmission</li>
<li>Direct drawing toroidal transformer for complete elimination of signal transmission loss</li>
<li>Exceptionally low impedance through secure screw connections</li>
<li>Superior quality electronic volume control for optimum sound</li>
<li>Discretely configured phono amp</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__label1:New</s:tag>
    <s:tag>__stock:260</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Yamaha</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_More than $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916223160371</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">6999.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>YAM-684282-A-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916222898227</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:40:35-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:40:35-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/yamaha-a-s2100-natural-sound-integrated-amplifier"/>
    <title>Yamaha A-S2100 Natural Sound Integrated Amplifier</title>
    <s:type>Amplifiers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Yamaha</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/71ezTEadE7L._SL1500_f1593074-52f1-490c-89cc-d5c281062297.jpg?v=1559061640"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Yamaha<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Amplifiers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            3499.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><h6>Relentless Pursuit of Musicality</h6>
<p>Audio is not just sound. If there’s music in it, that's an entirely different universe. For audio deserving the name “Hi-Fi” the need for high-definition sound is a given, and even more than that, high expressive power is demanded. Supreme quality sound, and dynamic expressive power are things we at Yamaha, as a premier musical instrument maker, have always pursued. This is the rich musicality of listening enjoyment. High-grade Hi-Fi components. The S2100 Series. An airy, open sound in which the most minute sounds reach the listener. Expressive power that conveys even the subtlest nuances which the artist pours into the music. A realistic sensation that you are directly in front of the performer. These are the goals and overriding philosophy behind the sound and sophisticated technologies inherited from the flagship S3000 Series. Emotional &amp; Dynamic. The sound created by the S2100 Series, reverberating vibrantly in the ears, and reverberating vibrantly in your ears, and resonating in your heart.</p>
<h6>A-S2100</h6>
<p>This high-grade integrated amplifier has inherited the natural sound of Yamaha in the pursuit of rich musicality. Advanced original amplifier circuitry and elimination of signal loss has resulted in a truly dynamic, affecting sound.</p>
<ul>
<li>Floating and balanced power amplifier with MOSFETs</li>
<li>All-stage fully discrete construction, balanced transmission and low impedance design</li>
<li>Superior quality electronic volume control for optimum sound</li>
<li>Large capacity power supply unit delivers energetic, dynamic sound with fast response</li>
<li>Symmetrical design in pursuit of ideal stereo reproduction</li>
<li>Discretely configured phono amp</li>
<li>Headphone amp with fully discrete configuration</li>
<li>Level meters visually reflect the dynamics in the music</li>
<li>Elegant design with luxurious real wood panels</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:53</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Yamaha</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_More than $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916222898227</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">3499.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>YAM-416238-A-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916218998835</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:36:17-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:36:17-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sony-str-za810es-7-2-channel-hi-res-wi-fi-network-av-receiver"/>
    <title>Sony STR-ZA810ES 7.2-Ch Hi-Res Wi-Fi Network A/V Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sony</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13899_538__4_da9eaa7e-4699-423b-a629-573d1bdebaf9.jpg?v=1559061382"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sony<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            698.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Enjoy flexible connectivity, powerful configurability and renowned ES quality in this 7.2 channel 4K AV receiver with Dolby Atmos and DTS: x object-based surround sound. Add in full 4K HDR compatibility and easy IP integration with leading control systems and you have the total package of installation-friendly features and audio/video performance.</p>

<h6>7.2 channels for deeply immersive surround sound</h6>
<p>Lose yourself in every soundtrack thanks to 7.2 channels of room-filling surround sound, with 100 W of power per channel. You can connect up to two active subwoofers for even bass distribution around the room. So whether you’re watching movies, playing games, or listening to your favorite songs, you’ll enjoy a next-level entertainment experience.</p>

<h6>Dolby Atmos</h6>
<p>Atmos treats sounds as separate objects, releasing them from typical channels to move freely around and even above you, for deeply immersive surround sound.</p>

<h6>Seamless auto-calibration</h6>
<p>DCAC EX uses a stereo mic to measure speaker positioning down to the nearest centimeter, before automatically adjusting frequencies, phase, and delays for better sound positioning. It then tunes your speakers using a 31-band EQ, for a listening experience that's tailored to your room.</p>

<h6>DTS:X</h6>
<p>DTS:X can create an unlimited number of audio objects which adapt to your speakers in real time, to give you total immersion in every movie soundtrack.</p>

<h6>Enjoy consistent 4K content</h6>
<p>Maintain 4K quality from source to screen—the 4K pass-through feature allows data to pass through the receiver without compromising image quality, and is HDCP 2.2-compatible.</p>

<h6>See more with 4K upscale</h6>
<p>Video upscaling gives you higher quality and more visible detail, so you can see more detail in everything.</p>

<h6>6 x HDMI inputs, 2 x HDMI outputs</h6>
<p>Bring all your home theater together. With 6 HDMI inputs you can connect an Internet TV box, Blu-ray Disc™ player and games console all at once, and still have room to expand.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<p>Enjoy flexible connectivity and high-fidelity sound from this 7.2-channel 4K AV receiver with Dolby Atmos® and DTS:X object-based surround sound. eARC1314 lets you enjoy these latest audio formats with one-cable HDMI connection from your compatible TV. Add in full 4K HDR compatibility and easy IP integration with leading control systems and you have the total package of installation-friendly features and audio/video performance.</p>
<ul>
<li>High-Resolution Audio capable</li>
<li>100W per channel power output</li>
<li>4K upscaling HDMI, 6-in, 2-out</li>
<li>Dolby Atmos® and DTS:X compatible</li>
<li>4K pass-through, HDCP 2.2 compatible</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:130</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sony</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$500 to $800</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916218998835</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">698.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SON-692802-STR-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916218409011</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:35:36-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:35:36-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sony-ps-hx500-hi-res-usb-turntable"/>
    <title>Sony PS-HX500 Hi-Res USB Turntable</title>
    <s:type>Turntables</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sony</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/11910_163__1_d6abac00-2eb0-4f32-ab5b-40a3b1be2c70.jpg?v=1559124626"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sony<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Turntables<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            398.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Meet the turntable that plays records and lets you convert tracks to portable, Hi-Res Audio for the authentic sound of vinyl that goes with you. Sit back and enjoy superior quality analog sound or plug it into your PC to digitally capture the music at its best for personal listening on compatible Hi-Res Audio players. It's vinyl reborn.</p>
<p>Enjoy all the smooth and warm sound expressions of your vinyl thanks to high-quality audio technologies that ensure the best possible analog playback. The integrated shell improves durability and stabilizes the cartridge for superior focusing and dimensionality of sound, while its lightweight structure improves traceability.</p>
<em>Supports both phono and line output so you can play through integrated amp or external phono EQ.Turntable Speed - 33 1/3 r/min, 45 r/min.</em>
<h6>High-quality audio technology for the best analog sound</h6>
<p>Enjoy all the smooth and warm sound expressions of your vinyl thanks to high-quality audio technologies that ensure the best possible analog playback.</p>
<h6>New tonearm design</h6>
<p>The integrated shell improves durability and stabilizes the cartridge for superior focusing and dimensionality of sound, while its lightweight structure improves traceability.</p>
<h6>Built-in Phono EQ</h6>
<p>Supports both phono and line output so you can play through integrated amp or external phono EQ.</p>
<h6>Digitally capture analog in Hi-Res Audio</h6>
<p>Breathe new life into analog masterpieces with Hi-Res audio up to DSD quality. Just hook up the PS-HX500 turntable to your PC via USB, play a record and digitally archive the music from your favorite vinyl recordings in Hi-Res.</p>
<h6>Vinyl goes portable</h6>
<p>The HX500's supplied software lets you use a PC or Mac to conveniently edit tracks from both sides of an album and transfer them in high resolution to a compatible portable player or device for playback—anywhere and anytime.</p>
<h6>Stability in motion</h6>
<p>The PS-HX500 turntable uses the latest techniques to deliver extremely stable rotation for optimal and natural delivery of your music.</p>
<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Highly stable belt drive system: the optimized spindle-bearing construction stabilizes the belt drive to achieve natural sound reproduction.</li>
<li>High quality 0.20-inch rubber mat: excellent adherence to the record’s surface minimizes unnecessary resonance for clean sound.</li>
<li>Aluminum die cast platter: the high-inertia aluminum die cast platter offers superb balance between strength and mass.</li>
<li>Acoustic-grade MDF cabinet: the 1.18-inch thick MDF cabinet has excellent sonic characteristics for accurate soundstage reproduction.</li>
<li>Insulated structure: the entire turntable structure is thoroughly insulated, including rubber dampers to eliminate vibration from racks and other peripherals.</li>
<li>Glass epoxy circuit board: using glass epoxy resin for the circuit board helps to provide better sound quality and stability.</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:137</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sony</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Turntables</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916218409011</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">398.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SON-569350-PS--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916215787571</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:33:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:33:00-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/shure-se215m-spe-special-edition-sound-isolatingtm-earphones-with-remote-mic"/>
    <title>Shure SE215m+SPE Special Edition Sound Isolating Earphones with Remote + Mic</title>
    <s:type>Turntables</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Shure</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/1867d5e66df5596d1ab8e5d93f23ca80_e23abd10-77ba-468f-860b-592efbcb1f69.jpg?v=1559061182"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Shure<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Turntables<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            119.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><h6>Special Edition White version of the legendary Shure SE215 professional in-ear headphones for hands-free use with Apple devices</h6>
<p>The SE215 delivers detailed sound with enhanced bass. A detachable cable with formable wire enables easy replacement and a secure, comfortable fit onstage or on-the-go. Sound Isolating sleeves in multiple sizes provide up to 37 dB of isolation and a customized fit.</p>
<p>Evolved from personal monitor technology that's been road-tested by pro musicians, the SE215 offers detailed sound for personal listening or professional monitoring.</p>
<h6>Immersive audio</h6>
<p>Own your audio space with Sound Isolating™ design that eliminates noise and keeps your experience pristine. It’s the right way to listen and the only way to really hear</p>
<h6>Get comfortable</h6>
<p>A complete fit kit of custom sleeves makes your earphones uniquely yours. Settle in for marathon listening sessions with audio that feels better and stays securely in place</p>
<h6>Take it on the road</h6>
<p>All premium components and cables are meant to withstand professional, performance-level wear and tear. See what we’re made of</p>
<h6>You’ve got options</h6>
<p>The SE215 cable accessories fit Apple iOS and Android with 3.5 mm, Lightning and USB-C connectivity. For wireless listening, easily add Bluetooth</p>
<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Dynamic MicroDriver produces a warm, detailed sound with resonant bass</li>
<li>Detachable, durable reinforced cable</li>
<li>Sound isolating design blocks up to 37 dB of ambient noise</li>
<li>Fit Kit with various sizes of foam and silicone sleeves provides sound isolation and optimises bass response</li>
<li>Over ear configuration keeps cables out of the way</li>
<li>Gold plated MMCX connector with lock snap mechanism allows 360-degree rotation for comfortable fit</li>
</ul>
<h6>Package contains:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Bluetooth 4.1 Communication Cable</li>
<li>Charging Cable</li>
<li>Clothing Clip</li>
<li>Zippered Carrying Case</li>
<li>Fit Kit with selection of Sleeves</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:272</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Shure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_White</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Earbuds</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916215787571</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">119.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SHU-138890-SE2-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916213297203</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:30:36-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:30:36-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/sennheiser-ch-800-s-high-end-headphones-cable-for-hd-800"/>
    <title>Sennheiser CH 800 S High-End Headphones Cable for HD 800</title>
    <s:type>Headphones</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Sennheiser</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/817r_2bnsbhnl._sl1500_de695eb2-cdfc-48ab-8713-9afb4f1af8db.jpg?v=1559118729"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Sennheiser<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Headphones<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            379.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>High-end cable for HD 800, optimally matched to HDVD 800 and HDVA 600 headphone amplifiers.</p>
<ul>
<li>Genuine Sennheiser CH 800S balanced Cable for HD800, HD800S Headphones with 4-pin male XLR Plug</li>
<li>Total Length: 11.5Ft (3.5m)</li>
<li>High-quality materials such as oxygen-free copper and gold-plated contacts for improved connection and signal transmission</li>
<li>Silver coating of the internal wires reduces resistance for enhanced electrical conductivity</li>
<li>Designed and made in Germany</li>
<li>Gold-plated contacts</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:126</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Audio Accessories</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Sennheiser</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Silver</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916213297203</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">379.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>SEN-465420-CLI-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916205432883</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:52-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:52-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-vsx-lx301-7-2-channel-networked-av-receiver-with-built-in-bluetooth-and-wi-fi"/>
    <title>Pioneer VSX-LX301 7.2-Ch Networked A/V Receiver with Built-In Bluetooth and Wi-Fi</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/cf527b1ec9b2c638ad84b561b487f4be_faee3599-f41d-403d-82ba-d75090c777c5.jpg?v=1559060574"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            700.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The VSX-LX301 features Dolby Atmos and DTS:X audio formats for fully-immersive surround sound. Connect to all your favorite music sources with support for the latest Dual Band Wi-Fi network connections to stream Google Cast, TuneIn, Deezer, and Tidal. The new 384kHz/32 bit DAC provides superior playback of all music resolutions from MP3s to Hi-Res audio files. Support for multi-room audio allows sources connected to the AV receiver to be played back in different rooms.</p>

<p>Google Cast, TIDAL, and Deezer require future firmware update. Deezer currently not available in US.</p>

<h6>DTS:X Ready</h6>
<p>DTS:X leverages object-based audio to enable immersive audio experiences. It automatically adapts audio to the existing channels and speaker system, so no specific speaker layout is required. Experience a soundscape with incredibly rich and life-like audio.</p>

<h6>General Specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>170 W/ch (6 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 0.9 %, 1ch Driven FTC)</li>
<li>100 W/ch (8 ohms, 20 Hz-20 kHz, THD 0.08 %, 2ch Driven FTC)</li>
<li>Ultra HD Pass-through with HDCP 2.2</li>
<li>Built-in Wi-Fi and Bluetooth</li>
<li>MCACC Auto Room Tuning</li>
<li>Dolby Atmos</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:280</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$500 to $800</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916205432883</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">700.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SAM-864377-43--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916205334579</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:44-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:44-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-vsx-lx103-elite-7-2-channel-network-a-v-receiver"/>
    <title>Pioneer VSX-LX103 Elite 7.2-Ch Network A/V Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/81fod-rsyyl._sl1500_46c1b819-d339-4aba-9a33-eeb06728b916.jpg?v=1559060570"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            499.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Featuring 5.2.2ch surround sound with Dolby Atmos and DTS:X optimized by MCACC, and spectacular view by Ultra HD video, HDR10, HLG, and Dolby Vision, the VSX-LX103 brings the thrills of the movie theater to your home. What's more, Flare Connect offers wireless multi-room audio with easy control on the Pioneer Remote App for various sources including vinyl records. Songs from internet radio and network streaming services can also be enjoyed with Chromecast built-in and DTS Play-Fi via your smartphone.</p>

<h6>Works with Sonos</h6>
<p>The awesome home theater you’ve built around your Elite receiver can now be part of your existing Sonos Home Sound System, or the start of a new one.</p>
<p>After a simple set up, your Elite A/V receiver will seamlessly tie into Sonos, instantly waking, changing inputs and playing at the volume you command through the familiar Sonos app.</p>

<h6>Dolby Atmos/Dolby Surround Upmixing</h6>
<p>Reproduce object-oriented sound in smooth, curving movements, or the realistic three-dimensional movement overhead by the top speakers. Other audio codecs including DTS formats can be upmixed using Dolby Surround for enjoying 3D surround sound.</p>

<h6>Next Generation Video Standard Ready</h6>
<p>All HDMI terminals support 4K (60p/4:4:4/24-bit), Wide Color Gamut (BT.2020), and HDCP 2.2, so you will have no problem when upgrading to new devices.</p>

<h6>Chromecast built-in</h6>
<p>Control audio from anywhere in the house using Chromecast enabled apps running on your personal device. The VSX-LX103 also works with the Google Assistant, so you can give voice commands via Google Assistant built-in devices such as Google Home to operate the AV receiver without lifting a finger.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Direct energy amplification at 170 W/Ch (6 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 10 %, 1Ch Driven)/ 80 W/Ch (8 ohms, 20 Hz-20 kHz, THD 0.08 %, 2Ch Driven, FTC)</li>
<li>4K Ultra HD pass-through with HDCP 2.2, Dolby vision compatible with HDR10, hlg and BT.2020 support (4K/60p/4: 4: 4/24-bit) and 1080p to 4K upscaling</li>
<li>Your Pioneer receiver can now be part of your existing Sonos Home Sound System, or the start of a new one. Instantly upgrade the music streaming capability of your home theater receiver with Sonos Connect and a free firmware update.</li>
<li>Ready for surround sound tracks with Dolby Atmos, Dolby Surround Upmixer, DTS:X, DTS Neural:X Upmixer and more</li>
<li>Multi-room audio with Chromecast built-in, DTS Play-Fi and Flare Connect</li>
<li>Music, Pandora, Spotify, Tidal, and Deezer music-streaming services ready and tune in internet radio</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:192</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916205334579</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">499.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-587425-VSX-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204613683</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:27-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:27-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-slim-audio-video-component-receiver-vsx-s520"/>
    <title>Pioneer Slim Audio &amp; Video Component Receiver Black (VSX-S520)</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/12973_849__2_af411f77-6937-4c5a-a2e9-11e9dbbf4221.jpg?v=1559060553"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            399.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Bringing quality sound and the latest Features in a slim and stylish design, thanks to a highly-efficient class D amplifier. Enjoy spectacular images with Ultra HD (4K/60p/4:4:4) upscale/pass-through, play Hi-Res audio via USB/network, listen to internet radio and various streaming services, or cast music with chrome cast built-in. The slim, stylish design and efficient power makes the VSX-S520 an ideal addition to any home Cinema, It is 120v.</p>

<h6>Built-in Dual Band Wi-Fi</h6>
<p>Enjoy network features such as audio streaming via wireless LAN connection. The built-in Wi-Fi is dual band, supporting both 5 GHz and 2.4 GHz frequency channels. By using the 5 GHz band, you can enjoy steady and uninterrupted streaming of audio files.</p>

<h6>Ultra HD Upscaling/Pass-Through with HDCP 2.2</h6>
<p>The feature lets you take advantage of the highest-quality video source for viewing on a 4K TV. With support for HDCP 2.2, you can enjoy premium content such as 4K videos with digital copy protection on a compatible display.</p>

<h6>Next Generation Video Standard Ready</h6>
<p>The VSX-S520 is ready for the next generation video standard HDR (High Dynamic Range) and BT.2020, which were adopted by Ultra HD Blu-ray. HDR is a technology that drastically expands the brightness peak, providing a higher contrast between light and dark images, which creates even more life-like pictures. BT.2020 is a new color-recording technology allowing a much wider gamut than the current BT.709 standard, enabling vividly rich coloration.</p>

<h6>MCACC Auto Room Tuning</h6>
<p>Create the optimum acoustic environment with Pioneer’s MCACC (Multi-Channel Acoustic Calibration System), developed with the expertise of professional recording studios. With the custom microphone, the system automatically compensates for differences in speaker size, level and distance, and equalizes response. As an innovative solution for the phase lag between the subwoofer and the main channel speakers caused by the network filter, Phase Control compensates the delayed bass to improve sound synchronization.</p>

<h6>Multi-room Audio Offers a Variety of Ways to Enjoy Music</h6>
<p>The VSX-S520 will support FireConnect Powered by Blackfire with a future firmware update. FireConnect is a stable wireless protocol that streams audio from a compatible Pioneer AV Receiver to a compatible Pioneer wireless speaker. Enjoy Bluetooth audio, front USB audio files and internet radio from the FireConnect compatible Pioneer AV receiver to an optional FireConnect compatible Pioneer wireless speaker(s) located in another room(s).</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Slim, 2.76” low-profile design 5.1 Ch network A/V receiver featuring MCACC room calibration. Dolby Atoms: 3.1.2Ch</li>
<li>Ultra HD pass-through (4K UltraHD 60p/4: 4: 4/HDR.10/BT.2020) with HDCP 2.2 and 4K upscaling (1080p to 4K)</li>
<li>Highly-efficient class D amplifier driving 80 W/Ch (4 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 1.0 %, 1Ch Driven FTC); 50 W/Ch (4 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 1.0 %, 2Ch Driven FTC)</li>
<li>Music file playback: MP3, WMA, AAC, Apple lossless, WAV, FLAC, AIFF, DSD via USB and network (Up to 192kHz/24-bit). sound delay (Lip Sync): 500 ms at 48K/ 400 ms at 96K/ 200 ms at 192K</li>
<li>Enjoy limitless streams of your favorite online music and internet radio stations including Spotify and for the first time tune in, Tidal, and Deeper</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:245</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204613683</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">399.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-108512-SLI-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204187699</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:17-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:17-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-pl-990-automatic-stereo-turntable"/>
    <title>Pioneer PL-990 Automatic Stereo Turntable</title>
    <s:type>Turntables</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/11337_041__1_2371cb96-e9a6-41e3-a153-5fe90ebf0744.jpg?v=1559060540"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Turntables<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            179.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The PL-990 is a fully automatic turntable with a built-in phono equalizer that has the ability to connect directly to a line or auxiliary input. It also includes a moving magnet cartridge that has a diamond stylus.</p>

<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Two speeds so you can play LPs and 45s</li>
<li>Fully automatic operation means you push a single button to play a record and the unit automatically suts itself off</li>
<li>Low-mass straight tone arm: Highly sensitive and resistant to resonance, track records better</li>
<li>Universal-type cartridge connector</li>
<li>Moving magnet cartridge included</li>
<li>Built-in phono Equalizer - Simply connect to any auxilliary/line Input on your amplifier or mini Audio system</li>
<li>P-mount cartridge</li>
<li>Low-vibration, belt-drive design</li>
<li>Rubber platter mat</li>
<li>Vibration-absorbing feet</li>
<li>Hinged dust cover</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__label1:New</s:tag>
    <s:tag>__stock:262</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$100 to $250</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Turntables</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916204187699</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">179.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-987561-SE--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203696179</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:22:07-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:22:07-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-hi-res-digital-audio-player-xdp-300rs"/>
    <title>Pioneer Hi-Res Digital Audio Player XDP-300R(S)</title>
    <s:type>Walkmans</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/14051_165__1_baafaba0-2418-47b0-bf4a-4b9efca03e33.jpg?v=1559060531"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Walkmans<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            699.99
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Enjoy hi-res audio with the silver XDP-300R Digital Audio Player from Pioneer. This portable player features a 4.7" capacitive touchscreen display that makes navigating through favorite tracks and playlists easy and intuitive. The XDP-300R supports multiple audio formats, including up to 11.2 MHz DSD, 384 kHz/24-bit PCM, FLAC, ALAC, WAV, AIFF, and MQA files. It comes with 32GB of built-in memory and features dual microSD card slots for expanding the base storage even further. The XDP-300R is equipped with both 2.5mm balanced and 3.5mm headphone outputs. It also supports Bluetooth and Wi-Fi technology for streaming audio. Audio can also be played via the micro-USB-B/OTG digital output.</p>
<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>In addition to the DAC and amplifier of the highest class, also equipped with Android OS. Equipped with a high-resolution model / highest level of DAC and amplifier also corresponding to the balance output by two groups, adopting the audio-grade parts. 300R dedicated tuning</li>
<li>Equipped with ESS manufactured by DAC "ES9018K2M" amplifier "SABRE9601K" one by each of the two groups</li>
<li>Corresponds to the most recent "MQA". MQA Limited is corresponding to the reproduction of became the developer "MQA" / â— 2 one of balance drive that you can select according to preference</li>
<li>High Precision EQ-HD / Club Sound Boost</li>
<li>High precision graphic equalizer which can adjust the volume of up to 16,384 band (frequency band)</li>
</ul>
<h6>Playback a Multitude of High Quality Audio Sources</h6>
<p>The XDP-300R supports all your current audio from MP3’s to streaming music from your favorite internet apps. With playback support for up to 11.2MHz DSD, 384kHz/24 bit PCM, FLAC, ALAC, WAV, AIFF, and MQA it is possible to enjoy many existing Hi-Res audio formats. Equipped with both 2.5 mm balanced output and 3.5 mm headphone output; audio can also be output via Micro USB-B/OTG digital output, and wireless output to connect the XDP-300R offers a wide selection of headphones and peripherals. Compatible Formats: DSD(DSF/DSDIFF)/FLAC/ALAC/WAV/AIFF/MQA/OggVorbis/MP3/AAC.</p>
<h6>High Resolution Playback with Twin DAC &amp; Amp Setup</h6>
<p>Incorporating twin unit ESS Technology DAC “ES9018K2M” and AMP “SABRE 9601K” each allows for extreme high resolution audio and component audio design philosophy while still maintaining a realistic power envelop for a portable device.</p>
<h6>Large capacity storage and battery life</h6>
<p>Equipped with 2 micro SD card slots (up to 200GBs each) ,the internal memory of 32GBs (including system area), have access to up to 432GBs of storage for music, movies, and apps. With up to 16 hours of Hi-Res audio playback, play to your heart's content.</p>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:146</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Silver</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$500 to $800</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Walkmans</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203696179</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">699.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-434147-HI--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203171891</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:21:57-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:21:57-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/pioneer-elite-slim-receiver-audio-video-component-receiver-sx-s30"/>
    <title>Pioneer SX-S30 Elite Slim Receiver Audio &amp; Video Component Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Pioneer</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/13120_704__1_e925be8b-8a59-4b3f-a872-ef8d8cce230d.jpg?v=1559060521"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Pioneer<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            449.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>With the Pioneer Elite SX-S30 you can enjoy various audio entertainment including Hi-Res audio files, music streaming services, internet radio, CDs, and vinyl records. Being equipped with Bluetooth wireless technology, airplay, and built-in Wi-Fi, you can wirelessly stream songs. With the built in Class-D amplification and thin design, this network receiver can fit in small places. If you have a streaming device, you can listen to songs by plugging them to the HDMI terminal. Just connect the speaker of your choice, and play and listen the way you like.</p>

<h6>Hi-Res Audio File Playback via USB/Network</h6>
<p>You can play up to 5.6 MHz DSD (Direct Stream Digital) files, and up to 192 kHz/24-bit WAV, FLAC, AIFF, and Apple Lossless files from a USB device or via wired or wireless network.</p>

<h6>Versatile Connectivity</h6>
<p>The SX-S30 is equipped with the phono (MM) input for a vinyl record player, as well as optical and coaxial digital inputs for connecting other audio sources. The HDMI (HDCP 2.2) terminal lets you connect to your streaming devices’ and enjoy audio streaming.</p>

<h6>Connect with AirPlay and Wi-Fi</h6>
<p>After connecting your SX-S30 to your home network, you can control/access your music library with the remote control, or play music from your phone or tablet using AirPlay.</p>

<h6>Wireless Multi-room Audio</h6>
<p>The SX-S30 will support FireConnect Powered by Blackfire with a future firmware update. FireConnect is a stable wireless protocol that streams audio from a compatible Pioneer Receiver to a compatible Pioneer wireless speaker x 2. Enjoy Bluetooth audio, front USB audio files and internet radio from the FireConnect compatible Pioneer receiver to an optional FireConnect compatible Pioneer wireless speaker(s) located in another room(s).</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>5 W/Ch (4 ohms, 1 kHz, THD 1.0 %, 1Ch Driven) 2-ch network receiver with Class-D amplification</li>
<li>Built-in Bluetooth and Wi-Fi (dual band 5 GHz/2.4 GHz). Apple airplay Certified with Pandora, Spotify, Tidal, and Deezer music streaming services ready</li>
<li>HDMI 4 in/1 out (HDCP 2.2)</li>
<li>Hi-Res Audio file playback via USB/network and phono (mm) input for a vinyl record player</li>
<li>Chromecast built-in and DTS Play-Fi technology (via future firmware updates)</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__label1:New</s:tag>
    <s:tag>__stock:108</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Pioneer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916203171891</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">449.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>PIO-450969-ELI-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916202123315</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:21:23-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:21:23-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-tt42-fully-automatic-belt-drive-turntable-with-cartridge"/>
    <title>Marantz TT42 Fully Automatic Belt Drive Turntable</title>
    <s:type>Turntables</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/71CLrXGeyGL._SL1500_5294da24-1be6-4a63-8ef5-c0f0377818bf.png?v=1559060487"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Turntables<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            329.00 - 359.00
            <a href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-tt42-fully-automatic-belt-drive-turntable-with-cartridge">(2 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Combining classic turntable design with modern audio technologies, the Marantz TT42 Turntable plays back your vinyl collection with stunning audio quality. This turntable features a fully automatic mechanism that plays records with a touch of a button. A low-coloration tone arm, DC servo motor, and belt drive ensure pristine, interference-free playback.</p>

<ul>
<li>Enjoy your vinyl collection with stunning audio quality thanks to modern audio technologies.</li>
<li>Low-coloration tone arm, DC servo motor, and belt drive ensure pristine, interference-free playback.</li>
</ul>

<h6>Vinyl Record Playing with Modern Convenience</h6>
<p>Have you noticed the resurgence of vinyl record sales in recent years? Fueled by the fact that many treasured albums have not been issued in digital format, and with newer artists continuing to release music on vinyl, turntables are popping up in living rooms all over the world.</p>

<p>The Marantz TT42 Turntable combines old school record playing with convenient, high-performance features. The turntable is fully automatic: with a push of the "play" button, the tone arm precisely lifts itself onto the record groove, saving you the trouble of having to manually position the stylus. Once playback has concluded, the tone arm safely returns to its resting position without scuffing your record.</p>

<h6>A Quality Mechanism for High-Fidelity Playback</h6>
<p>The TT42 turntable is outfitted with a low-coloration tone arm that resists resonance for a clear, balanced sound. A high quality, moving magnet cartridge is preset at the factory for proper tracking and smooth response. In addition, the turntable's DC servo belt drive keeps the motor running at a constant speed for optimum performance. The TT42 is designed to produce a stunning, nuanced, and distortion-free audio performance.</p>

<p>A version of the TT42 with a phono preamp, the TT42P, which features built-in phono input circuitry, is also available to accommodate multi-channel receivers that lack a proper phono input.
</p>

<p>The Marantz TT42 Turntable comes complete with a clear plastic dust cover and is backed by a three-year limited warranty, subject to the full warranty terms and conditions.</p>

<h6>Package contains:</h6>
<ul>
<li>TT42 Turntable</li>
<li>Plastic Dust Cover</li>
<li>User's Manual</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:279</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Turntables</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916202123315</id>
      <title>Cartridge</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">329.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-913764-TT4-CA</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916202123315</id>
      <title>On-Board Phono EQ</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">359.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAS-253054-DYN-ON</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201926707</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:21:19-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:21:19-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-tt-15s1-reference-belt-drive-turntable-with-cartridge"/>
    <title>Marantz TT-15S1 Reference Belt Drive Turntable with Cartridge</title>
    <s:type>Turntables</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/51tge77swjl._sl1280_b0ce4a0d-b818-4bad-af83-8ee389c48eaf.jpg?v=1559060482"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Turntables<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            1499.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Analog recording is still very alive. Quality turntables are still in demand. Digital discs simply set new performance standards that turntables must meet. Many cherished records may never be issued on digital formats. Good turntables are now more important than ever. Marantz embraces an audiophile quality turntable with AC servo belt-drive and low-coloration tone arm to answer the need for a high performance source component for the analog record.</p>
<h6>General specifications:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Low-Resonance High-Density Acrylic Chassis and Platter</li>
<li>Floating Motor Mount Construction</li>
<li>Asynchronous AC Motor</li>
<li>Belt Drive System with Endless Silicon Belt</li>
<li>Anodized Aluminum Straight Type Tone Arm</li>
<li>Magnetic Type Anti-Skating Mechanism</li>
<li>Fine Adjustable Counter Weight</li>
<li>Solid Aluminum 3 points Support Feet</li>
<li>Wood Base, High Quality MM Cartridge</li>
<li>"Clever Clamp" by Souther Engineering</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:298</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Accessories</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_White</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$800 to $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Turntables</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201926707</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">1499.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-632313-TT4-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201861171</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:21:13-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:21:13-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-sr8012-surround-receiver"/>
    <title>Marantz SR8012 Surround Receiver</title>
    <s:type>Home Cinema</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/81njrne9l7l._sl1500.jpg?v=1559060478"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Home Cinema<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            2999.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Experience the peak of Marantz AV expertise in the new flagship SR8012 – the first-ever 11.2-channel Marantz receiver that raises the bar for home theater. Envelop yourself in thrilling and immersive surround sound with Dolby Atmos, DTS:X and Auro 3D, the latest codecs able to drive overhead speakers for a true 3D sound experience. The receiver's 11 high-quality amplifier stages enhance audio performance via carefully selected high-grade audio components including Marantz Hyper Dynamic Amplifier Modules, or HDAMs, used in Current Feedback topology. These pass the signal to the power stages, each providing 205W of pure Marantz power and finesse to drive a full 7.1.4-channel home cinema setup without the need for additional external amplifiers.</p>

<p>And the SR8012 uses advanced Marantz sound-tuning throughout, drawing in features from the company's Reference two-channel models, including a copper chassis and an oversized, shielded toroidal transformer built to Marantz specification — plus high-current main power supply capacitors also made to the Marantz engineers' exacting standards.</p>

<p>With built-in HEOS technology, the SR8012 becomes a part of a HEOS wireless multi-room music network, enabling you to enjoy your favorite music anywhere around your home. Explore, browse, and play music from your music library, online streaming music services, or thousands of internet radio stations, using the free HEOS app.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>11.2 channel AV Receiver with 205W per channel – Enough power to fill big rooms with renowned Marantz sound</li>
<li>Latest HDMI standard for future-proof compatibility – 4K/60 Hz full-rate pass-through, 4:4:4 color resolution, HDR, BT.2020, Dolby Vision and HLG (Hybrid Log Gamma) pass-through</li>
<li>High-end build-quality for the ultimate in audio performance – Single board per channel power amplifier design; centrally mounted, oversized toroidal transformer; copper-plated chassis</li>
<li>Extended connectivity: ready to feed a TV and projector in parallel, and even a display in a second room – Eight HDMI inputs (including one front) with full HDCP 2.2 support; Three HDMI outputs (including Zone 2)</li>
<li>HD video quality from existing DVDs or analog sources – Analog to HDMI conversion and SD to HD/4K Upscaling</li>
<li>Immersive 3D sound with effects from overhead – Dolby Atmos (up to 7.1.4 or 9.1.2), DTS:X™, and Auro-3D built-in</li>
<li>Access to almost unlimited online music sources – AirPlay, Bluetooth, Internet Radio, Spotify Connect, TIDAL, Deezer and more</li>
<li>Hassle-free installation, setup and operation – Color-coded speaker terminals, Setup Assistant, Marantz 2016 AVR Remote App</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:260</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_More than $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201861171</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">2999.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-289236-SR8-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201795635</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:21:08-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:21:08-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-sr6013-9-2-channel-full-4k-ultra-hd-network-av-surround-receiver-heos"/>
    <title>Marantz SR6013 9.2-Ch Full 4K Ultra HD Network A/V Surround Receiver HEOS</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/16468_948__1_f0874d9f-741a-462e-a4f3-a1feb89021d4.jpg?v=1559060472"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            1499.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Immerse yourself in premium sound and multi-dimensional audio with the Marantz SR6013 9.2 channel AV receiver. It features Dolby Atmos, DTS:X and DTS Virtual:X decoding for immersive home theater, and proprietary HDAM circuit boards for more detailed, dynamic sound. Eight HDMI inputs are fully compatible with the latest specifications, including 4K Ultra High Definition video, 60Hz video, HDR, Dolby Vision and Hybrid Log-Gamma.</p>

<p>Listen to all your favorite music from your smart devices via Bluetooth, AirPlay or the HEOS app. Control the SR6013 with your voice and Amazon Alexa — download the HEOS Home Entertainment skill and ask Alexa to play, pause or stop music, switch inputs for your different media players, turn up the volume and more.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Now available – Apple AirPlay 2</li>
<li>9.2 channel AV Receiver with 110 W per channel (8 Ohm, 20 Hz - 20 kHz, 0.08% 2ch Drive)</li>
<li>8 HDMI inputs (incl. 1 front) with full HDCP 2.2 support; 3 HDMI outputs</li>
<li>Analog to HDMI conversion and full rate 4K Upscaling</li>
<li>4K/60 Hz full-rate pass-through, Dolby Vision compatibility, HDR, HLG and BT.2020</li>
<li>Three-dimensional audio formats Dolby Atmos, DTS:X (up to 7.1.4 with an external 2ch amplifier) and DTS Virtual:X for height virtualization effects</li>
<li>eARC (Enhanced Audio Return channel) supports the transmission of 3D audio from your TV apps with a single HDMI connection</li>
<li>Stream music from Internet Radio, Spotify Connect, Pandora, SiriusXM, Amazon Music, TIDAL, Deezer and more with Bluetooth, Airplay2 or HEOS built-in</li>
<li>Built-in Wi-Fi with 2.4GHz/5GHz dual band support</li>
<li>Enjoy multi-room whole-home audio streaming with HEOS technology</li>
<li>Amazon Alexa voice control via the HEOS Home Entertainment skill</li>
<li>Marantz 2016 AVR remote app for control over the latest generation of Marantz network AV Receivers. Available on iOS and Android.</li>
<li>High Resolution DSD (2.8/5.6MHz), FLAC, ALAC and WAV support</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:206</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$800 to $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201795635</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">1499.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-514243-SR6-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201697331</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:21:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:21:00-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-sr5013-7-2-channel-av-receiver"/>
    <title>Marantz SR5013 7.2-Ch A/V Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/16467_682__2_05639d9a-dc25-4634-b5f0-a2b07cc1fd44.jpg?v=1559060466"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            999.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Enjoy high-definition home theater and multi-dimensional surround sound with the Marantz SR5013 7.2 channel AV receiver. It features Dolby Atmos, DTS:X and DTS Virtual:X decoding for immersive home theater, and proprietary HDAM circuit boards for more detailed, dynamic sound. Eight HDMI inputs are fully compatible with the latest specifications, including 4K Ultra High Definition video, 60Hz video, HDR, Dolby Vision and Hybrid Log-Gamma (HLG; via future firmware update).</p>

<p>Listen to all your favorite music from your smart devices via Bluetooth, AirPlay or the HEOS app. Control the SR5013 with your voice and Amazon Alexa — download the HEOS Home Entertainment skill and ask Alexa to play, pause or stop music, switch inputs for your different media players, turn up the volume and more.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>7.2 channel discrete power amplifier, 100W per channel (8-ohm, 20Hz – 20kHz, 0.08% THD)</li>
<li>8 HDMI inputs — including one HDMI input on the front panel — with full HDCP 2.2 support, plus two HDMI outputs</li>
<li>4K/60 Hz full-rate pass-through, 4:4:4 color resolution, HDR and BT.2020, plus Dolby Vision compatibility and Hybrid Log-Gamma (HLG)</li>
<li>Supports object-based audio formats Dolby Atmos, DTS:X and DTS Virtual:X processing</li>
<li>Ability to decode high-resolution audio ALAC, FLAC and WAV lossless files up to 24-bit/192-kHz — plus DSD 2.8MHz and 5.6MHz tracks let you enjoy music exactly as the artist intended</li>
<li>Marantz proprietary HDAM circuit boards for more detailed, dynamic sound</li>
<li>Built-in HEOS wireless multi-room audio technology</li>
<li>Amazon Alexa voice control via the HEOS Home Entertainment skill</li>
<li>Stream the most popular music services — like Spotify, Pandora, TuneIn, Deezer and many others — via Bluetooth, AirPlay 2 or the HEOS app</li>
<li>Now available – Apple AirPlay 2</li>
<li>Integrated Phono input to connect to your turntable</li>
<li>Optimize your audio experience with Audyssey MultEQ, Dynamic Volume and Dynamic EQ for a seamless setup within your listening environment</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:108</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$800 to $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201697331</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">999.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-845669-SR5-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201631795</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:20:54-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:20:54-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-sa10s1-sa-10-super-audio-cd-player"/>
    <title>Marantz SA-10 Super Audio CD Player</title>
    <s:type>Home Cinema</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/71lg8qwlybl._sl1500.jpg?v=1559060458"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Home Cinema<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            6999.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Super Audio CD player with USB DAC and digital inputs:</p>
<ul>
<li>All-new SACD-M3 transport mechanism for CD, Super Audio CD and more</li>
<li>Playback of high-resolution audio compilations on DVD-ROM</li>
<li>USB input for hi-res audio up to PCM / DXD 384kHz/32bit and DSD11.2MHz</li>
<li>Isolation of USB and digital inputs to remove noise from connected sources</li>
<li>Innovative upsampling to DSD and filtering using unique Marantz Musical Mastering - Stream technology</li>
<li>All-new custom-designed 1-bit direct Marantz Musical Mastering -Conversion from DSD to analogue</li>
<li>High-quality analogue output stage with Marantz HDAMs</li>
<li>Generous power supply using toroidal transformer</li>
<li>Dedicated headphone amplifier with all-discrete construction</li>
</ul>
<p>The new Marantz SA-10 is the latest model in a range of high-end players stretching all the way back to the dawn of CD: in the original CD-63, launched in 1983, it had the first high-end performance-tuned CD player, and that expertise has continued to be developed over more than 30 years. The SA-10 is designed to sets new standards, whether with music on disc or content streamed from a computer, and to become the New Reference in digital audio.</p>
<p>To achieve that, the SA-10 is a completely new design, drawing on all that experience in making great-sounding players but with virtually every part redesigned. That involved both innovation and some unique thinking, all in the cause of getting the best possible performance across a wide range of digital audio formats. The new model is an exceptional player of both CD and SACD discs, but can also play high-resolution music stored on computer-burned discs, as well as being a high-end digital to analogue converter for computer-stored music.</p>
<p>From the unique new disc transport designed for this player all the way through to a complete rethink of the way digital audio data is converted into analogue signals, the SA-10 is a ‘clean sheet’ design, the result of painstaking research and development and extensive listening in Marantz’s custom-built listening facilities. That’s symptomatic of the way Marantz has always done things: while it always aims for the most elegant engineering solution, the listening test is always the final arbiter. It’s all to do with that simple phrase running through the heart of everything the company does: ‘Because Music Matters’.</p>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:224</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Blu-Ray &amp; DVD Players</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Blue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_More than $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201631795</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">6999.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-329535-SA1-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201533491</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:20:47-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:20:47-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-sa-ki-ruby-integrated-amplifier"/>
    <title>Marantz SA-KI Ruby Integrated Amplifier</title>
    <s:type>Amplifiers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/kirubysa.jpg?v=1559060453"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Amplifiers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            3999.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Marantz has been designing and making amplifiers for more than 65 years, and for 40 of those the products have reflected expertise of Ken Ishiwata. Now, to mark his four decades with the company, the SA-KI Ruby SACD player has been developed and tuned by a highly experienced engineering team led by KI himself. Features the same disc mechanisms as the SA10 that play SACDs, CDs and compilations on CD-ROM or DVD-ROM.</p>

<p>The SA-KI Ruby includes an asynchronous USB input that handles formats up to PCM/DXD 384kHz/32bit and DSD11.2MHz and treats all digital music with a unique Marantz Musical Mastering technology. By up-converting all file formats to DSD, using advanced filtering and processing and direct 1-bit conversion to feed the analog outputs, the SA-KI Ruby delivers sound with remarkable clarity, effortless dynamics and exceptional presence—plus, features a laser-engraved Ken Ishiwata signature to commemorate his legacy.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Engineered and extensively tuned by legendary Marantz sound master Ken Ishiwata and his team, drawing on more than 35 years of Marantz expertise in CD players</li>
<li>Marantz-proprietary SACD/CD mechanism “SACDM-3” designed purely for audio</li>
<li>Playback of SACD/CD and compilations on CD-ROM and DVD-ROM</li>
<li>Asynchronous USB input for hi-res audio up to PCM/DXD 384kHz/32bit and DSD11.2MHz</li>
<li>Isolation of USB and digital inputs to block noise from connected sources</li>
<li>Innovative Marantz Musical Mastering “MMM-Stream” up-sampling to DSD and filtering</li>
<li>Custom-designed 1-bit direct “MMM–Conversion” from DSD to analog</li>
<li>New analog output stage with Marantz HDAM-SA3 technology and low impedance output</li>
<li>Power supply with toroidal transformer</li>
<li>Dedicated headphone amplifier with all-discrete HDAM-SA2 construction</li>
<li>Laser-engraved Ken Ishiwata signature and Ruby motif, marking Ishiwata’s 40-year Marantz legacy</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:35</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Blue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_More than $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201533491</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">3999.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-740820-SA--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201500723</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:20:41-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:20:41-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-pm-ki-ruby-integrated-amplifier"/>
    <title>Marantz PM-KI Ruby Integrated Amplifier</title>
    <s:type>Amplifiers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/marantz.jpg?v=1559060446"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Amplifiers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            3999.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Marantz has been designing and making amplifiers for more than 65 years, and for 40 of those the products have reflected expertise of Ken Ishiwata. Now, to mark his four decades with the company, the PM-KI Ruby amplifier has been developed and tuned by a highly experienced engineering team led by KI himself.</p>

<p>Features a fully discrete two-stage design with separate power supplies for the pre-amplifier and power amp — plus, a moving coil/moving magnet phono stage complete with Marantz Musical Premium Phono EQ circuit and Marantz HDAM technology for signal purity and exceptional audio quality. PM-KI Ruby is built on a vibration-resistant double layer chassis with thick aluminum panes for rigidity and features a laser-engraved Ken Ishiwata signature to commemorate his legacy.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>Engineered and extensively tuned legendary Marantz sound master Ken Ishiwata and his team, drawing on more than 65 years of Marantz amplifier design knowledge</li>
<li>Marantz high-resolution preamplifier stage with proprietary HDAM technology</li>
<li>Switching power amplifier design derived from flagship PM-10 amplifier</li>
<li>Generous output: 100W + 100W (into 8ohm), 200W + 200W (4ohm)</li>
<li>Fully-discrete, two-stage design for signal purity, with separate power supplies for preamp and power amplifier sections to reduce interference</li>
<li>Toroidal transformer dedicated to preamp for clarity and powerful sound</li>
<li>Current feedback design with newly-developed wide-range circuitry</li>
<li>HDAM® SA3 circuitry for clean signal and optimal dynamics</li>
<li>MM/MC Phono input with new discrete Marantz Musical Premium Phono EQ circuit</li>
<li>Thick nickel-plated copper independent input terminals for CD and Phono, plus Marantz-original high-quality/high-purity copper-plated speaker terminals</li>
<li>Linear volume control with new electric volume system</li>
<li>High-quality construction with double-layer chassis, 5mm thick aluminum top lid, solid aluminum front and copper-plated chassis</li>
<li>Laser-engraved Ken Ishiwata signature and Ruby motif, marking Ishiwata’s 40-year Marantz legacy</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:124</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Blue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_More than $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201500723</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">3999.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-272999-PM--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201467955</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:20:36-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:20:36-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-hi-fi-integrated-amplifier-pm6006"/>
    <title>Marantz PM6006 Hi-Fi Integrated Amplifier</title>
    <s:type>Amplifiers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/12269_523__2_45ac850b-eeaf-4dbe-9f4b-87b53b796d53.jpg?v=1559060440"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Amplifiers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            699.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>The PM6006 is an upgraded successor of the multi-award-winning PM6005. We've retained the pre-amp and power-amp sections that exclusively feature discrete components - not a single IC in sight of the signal path. The PM6006 is upgraded for peak current at the amplifier stage, which makes it possible to refine the sound for you in much more detail.</p><p>You can connect this superb integrated amplifier directly to a vast range of digital sources and use its superior 24bit/192kHz high current CS4398 DAC to create an unbelievably high level of audio enjoyment with new media. The unit now includes 2 optical and 1 coaxial digital inputs (an additional optical input from the predecessor, PM6005), and the complete digital section is fully shielded by an extra metal housing to ensure that the digital stage has no effect on the analog signal.</p>

<p>All of the original features—such as five-line audio input including phono, two-pairs of gold-plated speaker connections with the convenience of bi-wiring, and a remote handset—are all still there. The lower impedance shielded Toroidal transformer, as well as customized components and unique Marantz HDAM modules care for powerful, dynamic and detailed original Marantz sound. In short, the new PM6006 is a new star with excellent genes.</p>

<h6>Marantz HDAM Technology</h6>
<p>Marantz developed its own discrete circuit boards to replace standard IC's. These HDAM's consists of discrete surface mount components with short mirror image L/R signal paths. Those devices are doing exactly the same thing as the Op-Amps, but outperform the regular IC Op-amps dramatically in terms of the Slew Rate and reduced noise level, resulting in a much more dynamic, accurate and detailed sound. Over the years Marantz developed different types of the HDAM to improve quality and to fit to the special requirements of a product category like CD or amplifier.</p>

<h6>Current Feedback</h6>
<p>The Current Feedback amplifier technology provides wide-bandwidth and high-speed sound reproduction. In combination with the Toroidal Transformer, the PM6006's amplifier holds a massive energy reserve to drive even demanding speakers with absolute ease.</p>

<h6>Toroidal Transformer</h6>
<p>A Toroidal transformer has several advantages over a normal EI core transformer. It is very efficient and therefore delivers more power compared to the same size of an EI core transformer. In addition, due to its shape, the electromagnetic radiation and the mechanical vibration are extremely low all ending in a better sound quality.</p>

<h6>High Current Power Supply</h6>
<p>The power supply has high current high speed Shottky Barrier Diodes and high current storage capacitors that together provide wide dynamic range along with low impedance drive capability.</p>

<h6>Reference Quality D/A Conversion for Digital Input</h6>
<p>The PM6006 features high resolution D/A conversion and is equipped with the reference class CS4398 D/A converter, which provides up to 192 kHz/24 bit resolution for optimum fidelity with high resolution audio file types.</p>

<h6>Expanded Connectivity for Digital Inputs (2 Optical, 1 Coax) with Hi-res Audio Support</h6>
<p>1 Coax digital and 2 Optical digital inputs are now available to connect digital devices and play back Hi-res Audio (up to 192kHz/24bit PCM) through the PM6006's advanced audio circuitry. And the complete digital section is fully shielded by an extra metal housing to ensure that the digital stage has no effect on the analog signal.</p>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:279</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$500 to $800</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201467955</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">699.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-512592-HI--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201304115</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:20:22-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:20:22-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-av-audio-video-component-receiver-nr1608-works-with-alexa"/>
    <title>Marantz A/V Audio &amp; Video Component Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/14098_554__2_c074a653-91a5-4a86-a26c-fffc1f11bec9.jpg?v=1559060432"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            499.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>A thrilling high-quality AV receiver occupying minimal space: that's the NR1608. High current discrete power amplifiers on all 7 channels deliver astonishing power and clarity, and it delivers immersive 3D surround sound thanks to both Dolby Atmos and DTS:X decoders, yet at just a little more than 3 inches tall it’s slim enough to slip into any TV cabinet. It’s fully compatible with the latest HDMI and HDCP 2.2 specifications on all 8 HDMI inputs, and will pass all the latest video formats – 4K 60Hz video, 4:4:4 Pure Color sub-sampling, BT.2020, HDR and Dolby Vision – from Blu-ray players, set-top boxes, games consoles and streamed/download 4K Ultra HD content to an Ultra HD TV or projector. For future HDR broadcast content, HLG (Hybrid Log Gamma) pass-through will also be supported via a firmware update.</p>

<p>Bluetooth and AirPlay can stream music directly from portable devices, while HEOS wireless multi-room music integration allows the NR1608 to become part of a complete home-wide music system. Explore and play your own music library, online streaming music services and thousands of Internet radio stations, using the free HEOS app.</p>

<p>Bluetooth and AirPlay can stream music directly from portable devices, while HEOS wireless multi-room music integration allows the NR1608 to become part of a complete home-wide music system. Explore and play your own music library, online streaming music services and thousands of Internet radio stations, using the free HEOS app.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>7-channel discrete power amplifier, 50W per channel (8 ohm, 20 Hz – 20 kHz, 0.08% THD).</li>
<li>4K/60 Hz full-rate pass-through, 4:4:4 color resolution, HDR and BT.2020, plus Dolby Vision compatibility and Hybrid Log Gamma (HLG; via future firmware update)</li>
<li>8 HDMI inputs (incl. 1 front) with full HDCP 2.2 support</li>
<li>Dolby Atmos (up to 5.1.2) and DTS:X</li>
<li>Built-in Wi-Fi with 2.4GHz/5GHz dual band support</li>
<li>HEOS wireless multiroom integration</li>
<li>AirPlay 2, Bluetooth, TuneIn Internet Radio, Pandora, Spotify, Tidal, Deezer, Amazon Prime Music, SiriusXM, Napster, iHeartRadio, Sound Cloud, Network Audio Streaming</li>
<li>Now available – Apple AirPlay 2</li>
<li>DSD (2.8/5.6MHz), FLAC, ALAC and WAV support</li>
<li>Audyssey MultEQ, Dynamic Volume and Dynamic EQ</li>
<li>Intelligent ECO mode with off/on/auto setting</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:270</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201304115</id>
      <title>Works with Alexa</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">499.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-740121-AV--WO</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201304115</id>
      <title>Classic</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">499.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-274406-AV--CL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201009203</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:20:08-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:20:08-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-av-audio-video-component-receiver-nr1508"/>
    <title>Marantz NR1508 A/V Audio &amp; Video Component Receiver</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/14097_988__1_13986810-a209-4c08-98bb-390c1343026f.jpg?v=1559060420"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            399.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>A thrilling high-quality AV receiver occupying minimal space: that's the NR1608. High current discrete power amplifiers on all 7 channels deliver astonishing power and clarity, and it delivers immersive 3D surround sound thanks to both Dolby Atmos and DTS:X decoders, yet at just a little more than 3 inches tall it’s slim enough to slip into any TV cabinet. It’s fully compatible with the latest HDMI and HDCP 2.2 specifications on all 8 HDMI inputs, and will pass all the latest video formats – 4K 60Hz video, 4:4:4 Pure Color sub-sampling, BT.2020, HDR and Dolby Vision – from Blu-ray players, set-top boxes, games consoles and streamed/download 4K Ultra HD content to an Ultra HD TV or projector. For future HDR broadcast content, HLG (Hybrid Log Gamma) pass-through will also be supported via a firmware update.</p>

<p>Bluetooth and AirPlay can stream music directly from portable devices, while HEOS wireless multi-room music integration allows the NR1608 to become part of a complete home-wide music system. Explore and play your own music library, online streaming music services and thousands of Internet radio stations, using the free HEOS app.</p>

<p>Bluetooth and AirPlay can stream music directly from portable devices, while HEOS wireless multi-room music integration allows the NR1608 to become part of a complete home-wide music system. Explore and play your own music library, online streaming music services and thousands of Internet radio stations, using the free HEOS app.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>7-channel discrete power amplifier, 50W per channel (8 ohm, 20 Hz – 20 kHz, 0.08% THD).</li>
<li>4K/60 Hz full-rate pass-through, 4:4:4 color resolution, HDR and BT.2020, plus Dolby Vision compatibility and Hybrid Log Gamma (HLG; via future firmware update)</li>
<li>8 HDMI inputs (incl. 1 front) with full HDCP 2.2 support</li>
<li>Dolby Atmos (up to 5.1.2) and DTS:X</li>
<li>Built-in Wi-Fi with 2.4GHz/5GHz dual band support</li>
<li>HEOS wireless multiroom integration</li>
<li>AirPlay 2, Bluetooth, TuneIn Internet Radio, Pandora, Spotify, Tidal, Deezer, Amazon Prime Music, SiriusXM, Napster, iHeartRadio, Sound Cloud, Network Audio Streaming</li>
<li>Now available – Apple AirPlay 2</li>
<li>DSD (2.8/5.6MHz), FLAC, ALAC and WAV support</li>
<li>Audyssey MultEQ, Dynamic Volume and Dynamic EQ</li>
<li>Intelligent ECO mode with off/on/auto setting</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__stock:42</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$250 to $500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916201009203</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">399.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-388788-AV--DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916200845363</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T12:20:01-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T12:20:01-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/marantz-audio-video-receiver-audio-video-component-receiver-sr7012-works-with-alexa"/>
    <title>Marantz SR7012 A/V Receiver Audio &amp; Video Component Receiver, Works with Alexa</title>
    <s:type>A/V Receivers</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Marantz</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0065/3095/7363/products/14645_926__3_09586a4d-b72b-4297-9a6f-6fee95e14156.jpg?v=1559060407"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Marantz<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>A/V Receivers<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            999.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Marantz has long set the standard for AV receivers combining home theatre prowess with superb music ability, and the SR7012 takes that capability to unprecedented levels, combining the very latest technology for an immersive movie experience, including full 4K compatibility and unparalleled 3D surround sound decoding, with precision audio engineering and tuning.</p>

<p>Marantz doesn’t believe that home cinema performance should come at the expense of music playback, and the SR7012 is designed to sit at the heart of a complete high-end home entertainment system, with nine powerful amp channels built-in. It has a wide range of facilities to enable your favourite music to be shared and enjoyed, including network streaming, compatibility with ultra-high-resolution music formats, Bluetooth and Airplay for playback from portable devices, and the HEOS wireless multiroom system.</p>

<h6>Features:</h6>
<ul>
<li>9.2 channel AV Receiver with 200 W per channel</li>
<li>4K/60 Hz full-rate pass-through, 4:4:4 color resolution, HDR, BT.2020 , Dolby Vision and HLG (Hybrid Log Gamma) pass-through</li>
<li>8 HDMI inputs (incl. 1 front) with full HDCP 2.2 support; 3 HDMI outputs (incl. Zone 2)</li>
<li>Analogue to HDMI conversion and SD to HD/4K Upscaling</li>
<li>Dolby Atmos (up to 7.1.4 with an external 2ch amplifier), DTS:X™, and Auro-3D built-in</li>
<li>Built-in Wi-Fi with 2.4GHz/5GHz dual band support</li>
<li>Built-in HEOS Wireless Multi-Room Audio Technology</li>
<li>AirPlay 2, Bluetooth, Internet Radio, Spotify Connect, TIDAL, Deezer and more</li>
<li>Now available – Apple AirPlay 2</li>
<li>DSD (2.8/5.6MHz), FLAC, ALAC and WAV support</li>
<li>Audyssey MultEQ XT32, LFC, Sub EQ HT, Dynamic Volume and Dynamic EQ</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a demo store. This product can be bought on <a href="https://www.hideflifestyle.com/">HiDEF Lifestyle eshop</a>.</p>                
<em>All logos, images, descriptions and brands are the property of their respective owners.</em>                                                        </td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>__label1:New</s:tag>
    <s:tag>__stock:108</s:tag>
    <s:tag>A/V Receivers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Amplifiers</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bluetooth</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Brand_Marantz</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Color_Black</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Home Cinema</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Price_$800 to $1500</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Professional Audio</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://warehouse-theme-metal.myshopify.com/products/1916200845363</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">999.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>MAR-639142-AUD-DE</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
